!retime('syl', get_start_time(), get_start_time() + 160)!
✦
massara na sekai
What wonders will we behold?
nani wo kimi wa egaku
Take your hand, draw it across the world
guuzen no saikai wa totsuzen ni
Back when we first found one another
hotsureta ito tsumuide yuku
Our destinies had already begun to intertwine
unmei no saihai wa itazura ni
And yet, the hands of fate began to dastardly flip
hakushi no peeji mekuri meku
Towards a blank page, starting our lives anew
aa umare kawaru tabi ni
No matter how many times we may be reborn
kasaneta nukumori wo
We’ll always find our way back to each other
sagashiteru
Fate can never tear us apart
kimi to deai kimi to yuku
The place where our journey began
happii endo no sono saki de
In search of our own happy ending
arikitari de keredo itoshii
I will keep looking until I finally find
hibi wo sugoshitai yo
An ending where I’ll always be with you
kimi to warai kimi to naku
Sharing our heartfelt laughs and soul-crushing tears
baddo endo no sono saki de
No matter what the future holds in store for us
nandodemo kimi no te wo
Even as the wheels of fate start to turn
nigirishimeru kara
I’ll always be by your side