It's so soft and fluffy!
I'm glad you like it.
Thanks, Shiorin!
This is the best present ever!
Thank you, too, for the wonderful present you gave me.
There are so many pretty animals and plants.
I hope I can go see them with you someday.
We will!
Your condition's been stable
ever since we came to this farm.
We'll make it!
I'll even carry you on my back
and soar through the sky if we must!
Are you okay?
We spent the entire day shopping today...
You go rest up now.
I'm sorry, Hatsune.
All I ever do is make you worry...
I'm sorry...
Rise and shine! It's harvest time!
Yeah!
Somebody's energetic this morning.
We're counting on ya.
Okay!
This soil is well-drained.
I can tell they take good care of it every day.
Huh... So this is the plant the spice comes from?
Karyl, here. Smell this.
It smells great!
It makes my stomach roar.
Doesn't it?
Morning!
Did you take a good, long rest from your journey?
Heya!
Yes, we're supercharged now!
Came here by foot this time?
I need to be in tip-top shape for the harvest.
My superpowers tire me out,
so I'm holding off for today!
Ah, sorry! Forget everything I just said!
H-Hold on!
So you're saying that wasn't magic,
but some superpower?
I've never met anyone with superpowers before.
A miracle...
The cat's out of the bag now.
You all seem like nice people,
so let's keep it between us, okay?
Oh, so it's our own little secret! Isn't that crazy?
Take it more seriously!
At least be somewhat rattled, will you?
W-We've got trouble!
Miss Rima?
Kokkoro?
What in the world happened?
O-On our way over here, we were ambushed
by something that looked just like us.
Then a swordswoman showed up,
dressed entirely in black...
Was Shiorin not with you?
I'm sorry. We lost sight of her when we were attacked.
Rima did the best she could!
She fought with all her might, and despite being
beaten up so badly, she managed to carry us back here!
Miss Rima, allow me to attend to your wounds.
Thanks, Kokkoro. What are you doing here?
We also came to help with the harvest.
So the rumours are true!
Many travellers have supposedly
been encountering these shadowy figures.
Come to think of it,
didn't the innkeeper go missing recently?
Excuse me!
Shiorin...
Perhaps I should have held back a little.
So that's what those Shadows look like.
What in the world is she trying to accomplish?
Whatever.
There's nobody in the world
who can quench my bloodthirst the way she can.
I believe it's time for act two.
Make more... Make more...
Now that's fun.
What melody will you play for me next?
Now, come! We shall put on a grand show!
Let me go! I have to go save Shiorin!
Calm down. You can't do it alone.
Wait!
I'll go with you!
Shiori was beyond excited
to finally see you again!
Miss Rima...
I'll go, too.
Yuuki?
Team B-B doesn't abandon those who need help!
Th-That's right. We're Team B-B!
If someone's in trouble,
we help them, no questions asked!
That's the kind of people we strive to become!
My lord, I will go with you.
You guys...
Thank you!
Karyl, we should also—
Karyl?
Ya think our Peco lady's harvesting right now?
'Spose so.
I can't wait for her to prepare that dish
with the legendary spice when she gets back.
I'm psyched, Bro!
I know!
Look at that. That's our Landosol Castle.
Wow, sure's pretty.
A toast to another day in our beautiful, peaceful Landosol.
Cheers!
I don't like this. Something's odd.
'Tis scary here.
I don't like this.
Miss Rima, how are your injuries?
All better thanks to your healing magic!
The forest feels really strange.
It's as if it's holding its breath,
afraid of something...
I'll take a look from above.
Rimama?! Hatsune can fly?!
It's magic.
Not a superpower.
Shiorin, where are you?
What was that?!
Miss Hatsune!
Hatsune!
Was that what I think...?
Shiorin!
Thank goodness you're all right!
Shiorin?
Enchanted Arrow.
Why, Shiorin?
Make more. Make more.
Make more of me.
Hatsune!
That arrow...
You mean that attack earlier was...
Shiorin...
Let's go.
He's right! Let's go find out what's going on!
I'll find her again and confirm for myself!
So they're going through with it, huh?
She's got to be the instigator behind this.
My mission is simply to observe Pecorine.
Nobody told me the Shadows were gonna be involved!
If we don't stop them,
the entire village could be...
Karyl!
You don't need to yell.
I can hear you just fine.
Karyl!
I'm so relieved!
Relieved?
You looked down earlier,
so I was wondering if you were okay.
H-How'd I look down?
I'm no different from usual.
Sorry for not being a happy camper like you!
Wh-What do you want?
Yeah! This is how you ought to be!
D-Don't be silly.
Come on! Let's go with Yuuki
and the others and look for Shiori!
Those voices...
Wai—Pecorine!
Make more... Make more...
Save me!
Help's coming right up!
You have nothing to fear.
I'll take care of these nasty monsters.
Thank you, lady!
Make more. Make more.
Make more of me.
Pecorine...
What's going on?
Is the village under attack?
W-We have to hurry back!
Not so fast.
A fun new act is about to begin.
Let's not dampen those spirits now.
Careful, everyone!
That's the swordswoman who attacked us!
Do you know what's going on here?
If you want to know so badly,
let's have our blades do the talking.
Rima!
My lord!
Yuuki!
Wake up! Now!
Open your eyes, Yuuki!
Good, you're still with me.
What about the others?!
This is basically a dream.
I just called your consciousness forth temporarily.
So the others are...
Kokkoro and the others are still in combat.
No. They can't even put up a fight against her.
They'll be slaughtered.
Send me back! Right now!
I wasn't expecting you to
encounter Christina again so soon.
Have I met her before?
Many times.
I doubt she even remembers that, though.
Understand this: I can't get involved with the real world yet.
The fate of Kokkoro and co lies on your shoulders.
The only way to put up a fight against Christina
is by unleashing your Princess Knight ability.
Princess... Knight?
You once made use of this power
before losing your memories.
Try to remember.
It's all yours,
for you and you alone, to use at will.
Remember the olden days
when you adventured with us.
What's wrong?
Is that all you had to offer?
I suppose that concludes this act, then.
...let you...
I won't let you!
Huh? What's going on?
This power...
I feel power welling up in me!
Let us advance.
Is this...
your power?
Here I come!
Metamorapple!
Rima, rima!
Many a thanks, Yuuki!
What?
I've got you now.
Wish upon a star!
Shooting Star!
I wish you luck!
Interesting.
Your party's power has grown so much,
they almost seem like different people.
And... this isn't magic, is it?
My lord!
State your name.
Yuuki.
This day has yielded
a greater harvest than I anticipated.
I haven't had such a good time in a while.
Oh, yes. As for that archer beast...
She's most likely been swallowed by a Shadow.
If she's still herself... Who knows?
Shiorin!
I can't forget.
My mission is to observe Pecorine and Yuuki.
I just... I just need to continue
keeping an eye on where this goes.
Yeah! This is how you ought to be!
My tummy's caving in...
I would've had a larger breakfast
had I known this would happen.
Make more... Make more...
What do you think you're doing, Pecorine?
We have to get rid of these fiends
and harvest a lot of spice, no?
Yes!
Are you ready for this?
Grim Burst!
Shiorin!
Don't give in! I'm coming to save you right now!
Hatsune?!
Are you all right?
Korosuke!
Exactly what the hell is going on?
I'm sorry, Hatsune...
I... can't...
Shiorin!
Stay strong, Shiorin!
We're getting out of here!
Hatsune?
Don't fall asleep, Shiorin!
Sleeping is my job!
Things will get hairy if you take over!
Come on, let's go!
I can't.
I'll only be a burden to you.
If this goes on, we'll both disappear.
So you have to get out of here,
even if you need to leave me behind.
Hwyatsune?
You're not a burden at all, Shiorin.
You always cheer me up!
Remember what I told you?
I'll just carry you on my back
and soar through the sky!
Make more... Make more...
Make more of me...
A Shadow!
I used too much of my power.
I made it this far, and yet...
Shiorin?
Thank you, Hatsune.
Thank you for always protecting me.
I hope that one day, I will be able to protect you.
That is my wish, and my goal.
I'm right here with you.
Enchanted Arrow!
Get out...
Get out of me!
That's...
Karyl!
I know!
Don't mess this up now!
Dark Vortex!
Full power! Full throttle!
Princess Strike!
Boy, talk about sloppy.
Did you skimp out on breakfast or something?
I sure am hungry.
Shiori?
Rima.
Thank goodness! She's back to normal!
Is Hatsune all right?!
She's... sound asleep?
Shh.
Wow! This is so good!
So good!