You're not gonna join them?
Yeah, good call. Friends are overrated anyway.
Being alone is so much easier.
I'd better get going.
There's something I must do.
They've prepared us breakfast, my lord.
Where could he have gone?
M-My lord!
It's fortunate they compensated us
so generously for those mushrooms.
Mushrooms. Great!
Yes, but...
I hope Miss Pecorine is all right.
Pecorine!
She said she was returning to Landosol,
so perhaps we'll meet her again.
Mhm.
Regardless, we must ensure we have
a place to stay by the time our money runs out.
What's this, lassie? Looking for cash?
Money. Important!
R-Right. That it is.
I can tell you two ain't used to town yet.
If you start a guild, the Guild Association
will lend ya a house to use as a base.
Really? I've never heard something so wonderful!
If you wanna make it here,
definitely consider startin' a guild.
Hey!
Don't go giving my customers any funny ideas.
My bad, bro.
Um, my lord...
Seeing you doing your best practising the blade
made me want to support you in some way.
So I made you this.
It doesn't serve much purpose, but...
Thanks.
Will do my best!
I'm glad!
Good morning.
Now, on to look for that sword Father gave me!
My stomach's howling...
I thought we were goners!
Man, if those crows hadn't saved our behinds...
I love crows!
Me, too! Love crows!
Now, let's go sell that sword
and make a pretty penny!
Yeah, yeah!
I hope we can find ourselves a well-paying job.
Wow!
Does she have an iron stomach or something?!
Delish!
May I have another plate, please?
Miss Pecorine?
Oh, if it isn't Kokkoro and Yuuki!
Heya!
Heya.
Thank you for escorting me to town yesterday!
A night's rest perked me right back up again!
Breakfast rules!
Ain't that crazy?
I'm glad to see you're doing all right.
So, as for what's going on...
Oh, this?
I was just helping myself to breakfast
in an eating contest!
What a perfect fit for
Miss Peculiarly Peckish Pecorine.
What's goin' on?
Oh! The beriberi man!
Please hold up! I have your medicine right here!
M-Miss Pecorine?
M-Miss, wait! Your prize money!
You forgot to accept your prize money!
And they're gone again.
Do you know those two men?
Yes! One of them has a disease called beriberi,
and I'm trying to give him his medicine.
Beriberi?
He didn't look very sickly to me.
What is it doing so close to human settlements?
It might hurt some townsfolk.
Leave this to me!
Miss Pecorine...
I had a hearty breakfast,
so I have a hundred times the energy now!
Ugh, sloppy.
I'll power you up, so bring me results!
You're not devastating this town on my watch!
That was very impressive.
I never would have thought
you could beat them bare-handed.
It would've been a bit easier if I had my sword, though.
Who is this?
First you simmer, simmer,
then boil up hot, hot.
Keep that rice snug...
Oh, she's awake, guys!
How are you feeling?
You're not hurt, are you?
Not feeling lightheaded or anything, right?!
G-Get out of my face!
Thank goodness.
She doesn't appear to be injured.
Mhm.
And you are?
My name is Kokkoro.
This is my lord, Lord Yuuki,
and that is Miss Pecorine.
"Pecorine"?
After that monster attack,
we found you unconscious nearby.
You've gotta be hungry, right?
We just finished cooking! It's super tasty!
Ow! Hot!
Hey! What's your problem?
Who shoves piping hot food in people's face?!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Here.
Ow! Still hot!
I don't want your crap!
I can't eat hot food, so stop force-feeding me!
I can get up on my own.
I don't need your help.
There's no way I'm thanking you.
I never asked for your help.
Owwie.
What is wrong with me?! I totally blew it!
I can't believe my target
nursed me back to health!
And what the hell is she playing at?
Why is she calling herself "Pecorine"?
Is she pulling my leg?!
Her name isn't Pecorine, but...
If she were to find out about this...
I will destroy her next time.
For her sake.
"Pecorine", I think she said?
So she really did lose her sword.
I thought it was special to her or something.
She didn't have it when I attacked her
at those ruins yesterday, either.
And with that last fight, I'm sure of it now!
I won't get a better chance!
Goddamn!
I never expected to see that chick in Landosol.
And here I thought we were gonna
have ourselves a party night!
Isn't that...?
Let's get outta here before she finds us again!
Loud and clear, Bro.
Y'know, Charlie...
Yo, das ya boi.
I was in this weird town the other day.
Uh-huh?
And this old hag tried to sell me
detergent outta nowhere.
Uh-huh?
Wait, what's goin' on? Is it about to rain?
A dragon? This close to the capital?!
Boy, did I just brew up the perfect plan!
I don't see him from him either.
Where could he have gone?
If only we could find some sort of clue.
Looking for something?
You're...
The girl who can't eat hot food!
Shut up!
I have a name, y'know! It's Karyl!
You can keep the labels to yourself!
Karyl?
Karyl! Wow! That's such a cute name!
That's crazy!
It's not crazy!
Calling someone's name crazy is rude! Rude!
That aside, it looked like you guys
were having some trouble.
Since you were nice to me before,
I figured I'd help you out if you need it.
Really?!
Well, we want to give this medicine
to the man with beriberi.
But we don't know where to find him.
Does he have any distinguishing features?
Y'know, like his looks,
or maybe he's carrying something?
Well, it's an older man with an afro,
and he's with a skinny younger man.
Oh, and they should be carrying a big sword!
A big sword, you say?
Do you know anything about them?
I have a good idea of where they may be.
You do?! Where?
A dragon carried them over that way, sword and all.
A dragon?!
C-Come to think of it, a flyer on
the Guild Association bulletin board
said that the dragon is attracted to riches
and has been sighted around Landosol recently.
I see.
It probably fancied their sword or something.
This is awful! They got into trouble because
they're looking after my sword for me!
What? That sword is yours, Miss Pecorine?
Yes! My father gave it to me.
I have a feeling things may be
more twisted than you realise...
Boy, you guys sure lucked out.
I know exactly where to find them.
You do, Karyl?!
I love you! Thank you!
Hey! Get off me!
There they are.
I-It certainly is large.
That's my sword! I'm sure of it!
And this is as far as I go.
No way I'm messing with that thing.
No worries, Karyl! Thanks for leading the way!
I-I'll wait for you somewhere safe nearby.
It's holding the sword securely in its mouth.
Mama!
Papa!
What's that chap doing?
Oh...
We'll save you soon, okay?
Y-You will?
We're counting on you, loony boy!
It ate him!
Grant us the blessing of the gods!
This is so reckless,
but my lord proposed this plan
because he has faith in me.
I will support him with everything I have!
Thanks for being bait, Yuuki!
I'm coming for you right now!
You fell for it splendidly, Pecorine.
Now I will crush you
with the power of my Princess Knight:
Monster manipulation!
Go! Kick her sorry ass!
Miss Pecorine!
Yes, just like that!
Keep it up!
My lord! Miss Pecorine!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's a miracle!
Oh, heya!
Sorry, I just grabbed at whatever I could!
I'm so sorry! I hope it doesn't hurt too much!
I'm fine! Have a little faith in my roots!
Okay!
You just don't give up, do you?
Have a taste of this!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
And down!
My roots!
Bro!
Now she'll finally acknowledge my talents!
She'll praise me!
Peco!
Nice one, Yuuki!
She did it!
Crap!
Pecorine?
Are you okay, Karyl?
You... got the...
Yes, I finally got it back!
M-My lord!
Yup! Nothing quite beats a sword
you can call your own!
Full power! Full throttle!
Princess Strike!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Seriously! We can't thank you enough!
Now, take your medicine.
Sure! I'll take whatever you want!
Bro!
My lord, please don't be so reckless.
Mhm.
Yuuki's quick wit saved me!
That was crazy!
Karyl!
I have to thank you, too!
Wha—B-But I didn't do anything...
We were only able to save them
because you guided us here!
I even got my beloved sword back!
Are—
Are you stupid?
Be seein' ya, Peco lady!
Until we meet again!
Righto!
Karyl, you should have dinner with us!
Huh?
It's cooled down now!
Kokkoro made rice balls
from the rice we cooked for lunch!
I-I'm good.
Rice really does give the ultimate energy boost!
It's delicious at any time of the day,
but it's on another level
when you get to eat together!
I was travelling alone for a very long time,
so I'm really happy I get to eat with you!
Crazy, right?
You're right. All I did was
press the leftover rice together, but...
It tashes weally ghood.
I know!
Why don't we start a gourmet guild together?
A guild?
Yeah!
A guild where we all work together
to find the most delicious delicacies!
We couldn't have asked for a better offer.
We've been wanting to start a guild, too.
Mhm!
Karyl! You should join, as well!
L-Like that's gonna happen!
When'd you count me in
with your little troupe, anyway?
I don't need your companionship.
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
What in the world am I doing?!
If I don't get my act together, she's going to...
Friends are overrated anyway.
Delicious.