Time to get this show on the road!
Our guild's objective
is to investigate and seek out every kind of
cuisine and ingredient to be found in the world!
And then to enjoy eating them together!
We'll call it the Gourmet Guild!
Let's get this party started!
Right here, right now!
Cough.
Bugs!
Gather 'round, people!
Excuse me, but what the hell?!
Is this a haunted mansion or something?
My deepest apologies.
We're a bit short on guild houses
to lend out at the moment.
Maybe not people, but what about those snakes
and centipede-looking things in there?!
This house wasn't the site of some
freak accident or something, right?
You need not worry about things like that.
It's just that
this might be the home of ghosts and other spectres...
Hold on! I could've sworn I heard "ghosts" there!
Nothing to worry about, Karyl.
I'm sure they'd be more than happy
to join us for dinner!
Wouldn't that be crazy?
Do you not care about who you're
dining with so long as you can dine?!
Give me a break already!
Even so, I'm glad we no longer
have to camp out in the elements.
Miss Karin, is it all right if we do
a little work to make it more liveable?
By all means.
Is everyone ready?
If we're doing this, we're being thorough!
Leave not a single speck of dust behind!
Yeah!
I never thought our first guild activity
would be spring cleaning.
Hey, Korosuke, could you wash
those curtains we took down?
Koro...
A-All right.
Heave-ho.
I think there was a basin in the closet.
You can use that.
Understood.
Splish, splash, splish, splash...
Splish, splash, splish, splash, splash...
There we go!
I think that was the last thing still inside.
Mhm!
Dresser, sofa... I'm not missing anything, am I?
What's the matter?
This is an emergency, Kokkoro!
This house has a major flaw!
Huh? What are you going on about?
It's already infested with snakes and bugs.
What could possibly be more of an emergency?
It's missing a key element!
It doesn't have a table to eat at!
Oh, now that you mention it.
So that's what you meant.
Just go to town and buy one then.
Karyl, what is the goal of the Gourmet Guild?
Huh? Oh, uh...
Eating?
No!
It's for all of us to enjoy our meals together!
Uh... Right...
The dining table is too precious
an element to pick on a whim!
So I will build the perfect table
for us to enjoy our meals on!
From scratch?
Lady Karyl.
What's up, Korosuke?
Koro...
I'd appreciate it if you could call me "Kokkoro"...
The minor details sure bother you, huh?
Well, indeed...
I'm off to go buy some essentials.
Please take care of the cleaning while I'm away.
You can count on me!
I'll have it all spic and span in no time!
It's a good thing we still have some money
from that dragon quest left.
But it's always best to be frugal.
I must be careful not to loosen
the purse strings too much!
Bug-free!
Snake-free!
And most importantly, gh-ghost...
Gulp...
Free!
Now I can go all in on cleaning.
That kinda looks like a human face...
These are very cute.
Oh?
Do those plates strike your fancy?
Yes.
But they're a bit over budget.
This is a bazaar.
Haggling is part of the fun.
I'll give you a deal!
Thank you very much.
Um, my name is Kokkoro.
And mine's Saren.
I'm the manager of the Sarendia Orphanage.
That is very admirable.
Not really. The children are the ones
giving me the strength I need.
Is there anything else you're looking for?
I'll cut you a special deal.
S-Stop!
S-Stoop!
S-Stooop!
S-Stoooop!
S-Stooooop!
S-Stoooooop!
S-Stooooooop!
S-Stoooooooop!
S-Stooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoop!
S-Stooop!
S-Stoooop!
S-Stooooop!
S-Stoooooop!
S-Stooooooop!
S-Stoooooooop!
S-Stooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
S-Stooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!
Somebody, save me!
What's going on?
I swear, that girl!
I'm so sorry, milady!
You could imagine my shock.
I thought I heard you calling out,
only to find you flying right past me.
I-I-I-I-I'm so sorry!
But I'm glad you don't seem to be hurt.
Yes, and our bazaar goods are still in one piece.
By the way, who might this be?
Pleased to meet you. My name is Kokkoro.
Oh, you're very polite.
My name is Suzume, and I have the honour
of serving as Lady Saren's maid.
I'm glad you're here.
I'll keep an eye on our booth.
Suzume, could you please help
carry Kokkoro's things for her?
Th-That won't be necessary!
That's too much for you to carry all by yourself.
Us ladies need to help each other out!
That's right!
Let's go load up the cart straight away!
Thank you so much.
Perfection!
If this isn't perfection, I don't know what is!
A fine job if I may say so myself!
Now I've just gotta keep up the pace.
Pecorine, how far have you gotten in the meantime?
Looks like it'll still take a while.
You have someone you serve as well?
Yes.
They are incredibly lucky to have
someone as adorable as you serving them!
Oh, heavens no...
I feel blessed to be able to serve my lord.
Have you been serving Lady Saren long?
Yes!
Milady used to be the vice captain of the palace knights,
but she abandoned her status to help children
without families or who were separated from their parents.
That's why she founded the Sarendia Orphanage.
I wanted to help her however I could in that endeavour.
How wonderful of both you and Lady Saren.
I-I'm not wonderful at all!
All I ever do is mess stuff up!
As do I.
I hope to one day share the kind of bond
with my lord that you do with Lady Saren.
You will. I know you can do it.
I won't give up.
Eep!
Where...
...are we?
P-Please don't worry!
W-We're just a teensy-weensy bit off course!
I-I understand...
But it's so dark despite it being the middle of the day.
There may even be monsters.
M-M-M-M-M-M-Monsters?!
Wh-Where?! Where are they?!
Th-There they are!
M-Miss Suzume, please calm down!
Are you all right?
I-I'm fine...
Wh-Where'd the donkey go?
Somewhere far away...
Wh-What do we do now?!
We can't pull the cart without the donkey!
That might be our donkey.
Is that...
The donkey? A horse?
I'm going to borrow this rope
that was in the cart.
We'll catch that animal and have it pull the cart.
That's a great idea, Kokkoro!
Rima-rima?!
I can't breathe!
Please don't eat me, rima!
It spoke!
You scared the daylights out of me, rima!
Does my hair look okay?
I styled it up so cute...
Well?
It doesn't look funny, does it?
M-May I ask you a question?
Are you a do—
I mean, a mon—um...
Excuse me? What part of me looks like
a donkey or a monster to you?!
Have you ever met a monster this cute?
Yes, I know I'm very fluffy, but sue me!
Indeed, you are...
And you can talk.
And I'm wearing the latest fashion!
I figured there was no way
I'd be mistaken for an animal.
What a shame!
Th-That ribbon looks lovely on you.
Really? You really think so?
I always get so giddy when people compliment me!
Whoopsie!
I'm sorry, force of habit.
The spit just comes flying out when I get excited!
I-It's okay...
I apologise for what I said before.
My name is Kokkoro.
I'm Suzume. Nice to meet you.
I'm Rima.
I work on a ranch just beyond
this forest, called Elizabeth Park.
What are you two doing this deep in the forest?
Well, we were pulling a cart,
but our donkey ran away.
That's awful!
Would you like me to pull your cart?
Would you?
I may look all cute, but I'm plenty strong, too!
Up we go.
It's not too heavy, is it, Miss Rima?
No problem!
A load like this is a piece of cake!
There we go.
Yuuki.
I want to wipe down those windows.
Could you give me a hand?
Mhm.
Yes, just like that!
They say a disorderly life reflects a disorderly mind.
This house will be the foundation of our lives
from now on, so we've gotta get it sparkling clean!
I don't get it.
Are you smart?
Of course I am! Are you mocking me?!
You ought to dive into the books a little yourself!
You can't rely on others
just because you've lost your memories.
Righto.
Hey! At least pretend you actually care!
Bugs! Bugs!
Hey! Are you okay?!
Hey... Hey, come on! Wake up!
Hi. Long time no see.
It looks like you've been through a lot,
but it seems you managed to start a guild.
Don't worry.
All you did was lose consciousness.
You've found a surprising
group of companions, though.
Your fellow guild founders are all
connected to the mystery of the world.
Mystery?
Yes.
What everyone in that world
naturally accepts as "the truth"
is actually anything but.
Pecorine and Karyl, and even Kokkoro.
Each have their own demons to overcome,
as well as their own missions.
Karyl in particular has it very rough.
Even if I told you everything I know,
it wouldn't solve anything.
Be careful.
The enemy is aware of your existence.
The bonds you form with those girls
will help you grow further.
When the time is ripe, I'll come to your aid.
Just like I did in the olden days.
Good luck.
Thank goodness.
This house almost became the site of
a freak accident right after we moved in!
Are you okay?
Karyl in particular has it very rough.
Mhm.
Looks like you're okay to me.
Yuuki! Karyl!
What do you think?
Really looks like we would enjoy our meals now, right?
You really are handy,
and I don't just mean at cooking.
Well, I set out on this journey to train, after all.
But I agree. I think we'd all enjoy
sitting around the table.
Nice!
Thank you!
Let's get it inside, pronto!
Yeah!
Oh my...
No worries.
Rima, rima, rima, rima, rima...
We appreciate your help.
I didn't know what we were gonna do!
Please, don't be so dramatic!
There aren't any monsters in this forest,
but we occasionally see—
They're here!
Bandits!
What?!
Yo! If you want to pass through here,
give that donkey to...
Wait, donkey? Horse?
You're so cruel! I'm all dressed up and everything!
It's not a donkey?!
Wh-Whatever! We'll grab it for the circus!
Stop!
We should get to know each other a bit better first!
Miss Rima!
It's really strong!
It's too fluffy to grab hold of!
Damn it! Hold still, donkey!
Snap!
I told you...
I am no donkey!
Have you ever seen a donkey this stylish?
Finishing move: Fluffy Strike!
Hmph!
I hate pushy people!
Rima...
I'm hungry after all that fighting.
This is precious, but I'd rather not starve.
Rima, rima, rima, rima...
Rima!
Eating a metamorapple
gives me a human body like everyone else!
Amazing, huh?
We got it all cleaned up before dark.
Perfect.
Korosuke's running kind of late, huh?
I'm getting worried. Should we go check on her?
Welcome back.
I have returned.
How'd it go? Did you find some nice things?
Yes, lots.
This is for you, my lord.
You're late, Korosuke.
Come take a look inside.
Wow...
I know, right?
Don't hold back! I know my cleaning skills
are out of this world!
Kokkoro!
This is...
Absolutely wonderful.
What do you think?
Crazy, isn't it?
Yes, most crazy indeed.
That should do it.
Milady!
You took your sweet time, Suzume.
Today I decided to make house-warming beef
to celebrate us moving into this house!
Have all the seconds and thirds
and fourths you like!
Isn't the restaurant owner nice?
This looks great!
Boy, I oh, so miss those bugs of yours.
Imagine if we had those as our first meal here.
Oh, we could always go for those instead!
I was being sarcastic!
Lady Pecorine, Lady Karyl.
I look forward to working with both of you.
You don't need to be so formal with us.
C'mon now, before dinner gets cold!
Thanks for the food!
Perfecto!