How come she's so damn strong?!
It's borderline cheating!
But, but, but...!
She must have some kind of weak point!
Tremble in fear, Pecorine. I'm coming for you.
My tummy's rumbling...
I'll bide my time until I find out
all about your weaknesses.
Hello!
Heya!
Ten plates of fried rice, extra large!
Thank you for your patronage!
The fried rice here is the best.
Peco lady!
Oh! The beriberi man!
Heya!
We've been looking all over for ya, Peco lady!
We still ain't thanked ya for saving our sorry hides!
There's this great restaurant
we go to all the time!
With tasty menus?! That's crazy!
Super duper crazy!
You'd like to apply?
Indeed. I've found some friends
I'd like to form a guild with.
Oh, my! I'm glad to hear that!
Let's get you registered right away then.
Oh, heavens no.
It doesn't have to be right now.
I was just hoping I could get
the application form for the time being.
I hope they'll agree to join your guild.
Me too.
Wh-Who are you?
You hungry?
My lord!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I got us the application form.
Mhm.
Well, shall we go?
I wonder where those two are.
Whoa, hang on!
You still want to eat more?
You utter imbecile! Don't you dare
underestimate our Peco lady!
There they are.
Oh?
Might that be...?
She still hasn't had her fill?
I've been starving out here because of you!
C'mon, show me your weaknesses already.
Then I'll finally snatch you up,
cut you into little bite-sized pieces, and then...
Heya.
S-Stop sneaking up behind people
before I kill you!
Good day to you, Miss Karyl.
What might you be doing over there?
N-N-N-Nothing...
I just felt like grabbing a bite,
so I wanted to see what they were serving here.
Our timing couldn't have been
more perfect, then.
Boss! Another serving, pretty please!
By the sounds of it,
Miss Pecorine is here as well.
Would you care to join us?
And exactly why should I eat together with—
Oh, it's y'all!
Heya!
Heya.
Ikacchi and Charlie just finished eating.
Come join me!
Y-Yeah... You guys go enjoy yourselves.
This restaurant's food really is delicious.
The best!
Isn't it?
You seem a bit low on energy, Karyl.
What's the matter? Are you anemic?
Eating tasty food will fix that!
By all means!
Seriously! Quit shoving food in my face!
Why's she acting like we go way back?
You haven't the slightest clue what I want to do!
Oh? Don't you like steak with potatoes?
Well, here's the menu. Order whatever you like!
Fish and chips, then.
No can do. We ain't got the ingredients.
This is all because you're such a damn glutton!
This mouth! It's this portal
to an infinite dimension's fault!
Ow! It hurts, Karyl! It hurts!
I suppose we should go to a different restaurant.
Nhot so fwast, Kokkowo!
I heard dis restaurant has a secwet menu!
A secret menu?
Miss, might I ask where you heard that?
It was Ikacchi.
Boss, we'll have the secret menu!
Well then, it's time to start today's
main event: the bug food party!
Yay!
Now hold on for one second!
D-Did I hear that right? B-Bug food?!
I mean food made out of bugs,
not food for bugs, by the way.
I don't get you!
Just what the hell is wrong with you?!
I'm quite intrigued by this concept.
Oh, come on, you guys!
Use your noggin!
Most people would pour
bug-ridden food down the drain!
Oh, come now, Karyl.
Don't-act-so-spoiled!
Please spare me!
Putting on an angelic smile doesn't make it any better!
Why aren't you guys stopping h—
You were right. It is quite delicious.
Try one, my lord.
Here.
Come on, you mite! Don't feed him bugs!
I thought he was your oh-so precious lord!
That's precisely why I want him
to eat a healthy variety of food.
At any time,
to eat is to live.
Exactly!
As your reward, have some bug flambé!
This is also delicious.
Okay, I've had it! I can't deal with you peo—
No way. It is good.
Told you!
I'm so glad you like it!
But I may have been a bit too excited.
Eating with all of you was so much fun, I couldn't hold back.
Sorry, I'll try toning it back a bit.
Hmph. I just happened to be hungry,
so I don't mind joining you this one time.
But only this time, you got that?
Yes!
In that case, have this caterpillar first!
I don't want the meaty things right away!
Start off with the light stuff first!
That was so yummy! I'm in heaven!
Couldn't they at least make it look more appealing?
The barrier to entry's off the charts!
Now, now.
Overcoming that barrier has
opened up many new doors for you!
You mean you forced open many new doors!
I can't believe you. I swear.
Um, Miss Karyl, Miss Pecorine...
If I may, I know this is a bit presumptuous of me,
but I picked up a guild application.
I was hoping we could start
a guild together, just the four of us.
Thank you, Kokkoro!
You're such a sweet girl!
Not so fast.
I thought I was clear I'm not joining.
Sorry, but I'm seriously not interested.
So long. Also, thanks for treating me.
Damn it all! Just what am I doing?
My mission is to eliminate Pecorine!
So why am I sitting around the table with my target?!
I can still taste bug...
Now that hits the spot!
I bet this would've gone great with our lunch!
Well, you're awfully chipper, aren't you?
N-Not really.
These peaceful times are a real bore.
I can't help but find myself hoping
something more interesting will happen.
Don't you feel the same way?
I-I...
You're nothing like me.
What an adorable little kitten.
Part-time work?
Yes!
Y'see, I ran outta money, so...
You've got some potential
if you can appreciate my secret menu.
And then he hired me right on the spot!
I can't help but squeal in delight
at their flavours and ingredients.
It's a real honour to work there!
Welcome!
Oh, are you the new part-timer?
Excited, aren't we?
Really? Yay, caught a compliment!
You sure did, sunshine!
Man, you're super good, little lady!
Super good!
The road to forming a guild is a long one.
How crazy is that?
It's good.
How crazy crazy is that?
Their fish is excellent, too.
Mhm!
One lizard steak and a gelatina rice bowl, was it?
Boss! Another order, coming up!
You look like a real cutie pie, waitress!
Really? Ain't that crazy?
Super duper crazy!
Table three, order up.
Coming!
No, Misogi! Stop pushing me!
I've never been to a restaurant like this before!
Quiet! You'll disturb the other customers!
Oh, my? What cute little customers!
Welcome!
H-H-Hello!
Hello to you, too!
Help yourselves to any open table!
Th-Thanks!
Stop it, you two!
Aw, but it's fun.
You should try it, Kyouka.
I'm gonna tell your mom, Mimi.
Please don't....
Those are some cute little moustaches.
Is this your first time here?
D-Don't treat us like kids!
We're part of the guild, Little Lyrical!
I-It's not officially registered yet though,
since we're not old enough yet...
You have a lovely group of friends.
Th-Thanks.
Oh? You must be hungry, huh?
Have you decided what you'd like?
N-Not yet. There's so much to choose from.
What do you recommend, miss?
There's a ton of stuff I'd recommend!
What? Observe her?
Yes. We're calling off the assassination.
There's been a change of circumstances.
It has come to my attention that
you haven't become fully accustomed
to the power of the Princess Knight
I bestowed upon you.
P-Please forgive me.
Karyl.
How indecisive you are.
I will show you what path you are to follow.
Of course.
That's right. She will put me on the right path.
For her sake, I have to—
Here comes the airplane!
Open wide!
The hell?
Karyl!
What are you trying to feed these kids?!
And why are you dressed like that?!
How do I look?
I'm a waitress!
A waitress? You're working here?
Fidget, fidget...
Okay, listen! No means no,
so stop fidgeting behind me already!
Wait...
I forgot. I came here to join their guild.
L-Look... I sorta had something I wanted to tell you.
I mean... I guess I changed my m—
This the place that's been serving
nasty food with bugs in 'em?
Hey, you! Ya got somethin' to say
'bout boss's cooking?
Bro!
Hey! You lazy asses can serve bugs,
but not a single cup of water?
What'd you say about my restaurant?
Leave the yapping until
after you've had a taste of my—
Oopsie. Sorry, man! My hand slipped there!
Shit!
Are you grumpy because you're hungry?
What'll it be, darling?
You gonna go to the kitchen
to make me food in place of that old fart?
Tell ya what! If I think it tastes like dogshit,
I'll have you close up shop right now!
Landosol is a place where anyone,
no matter who they may be,
can enjoy a good meal.
Your order's coming right up!
Hallelujah...
She's incredibly skilled.
While on my journey, I've gotten by by making dinner
out of all sorts of animals, bugs, and even monsters.
Halle...
Do you even know how
this restaurant seasons its food?
The flavour of the boss's delicious bug dishes
is carved into my stomach,
my brain's recipe book.
I got this.
All done!
Hmph. Took you long enough.
You may not guess it, but I'm a foodie!
Ya gotta try if you wanna satisfy my palette!
If I crush their wills and they close up shop,
I'll be getting a pretty penny from their competitor.
Now, what's going down the hatch first, I wonder?
Man, that bug looks disgusting!
Wait.
Karyl?
This dish isn't complete yet.
A single drop of the blessed juice of this fruit
will have you hearing a chorus of angels.
What's that load of bull?
Th-This is...
Boy, this looks disgusting!
Impossible!
You've gotta be kidding! These are bugs!
What is this harmony of rich umami
and mellow flavour
that spreads through my mouth with each bite?!
I... I can hear them!
I hear voices singing!
It's... It's not...
It's not... It's not...
Say it! Just say it!
Say this food isn't any good at all!
It's... It's... It's not...
It's... It's... It's...
It's so good!
We did it, Karyl!
Don't screw with me!
Like hell could some nasty bugs taste any good!
I'll shut down any restaurant that serves bad food!
Bad boys who waste food
need to be punished.
Bad boy! Am I clear?
Way to go, Peco lady!
You're amazing!
Yay, Peco lady!
All right!
Have I perhaps grown a little, Father?
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
Here it is, my lord.
Karyl?
Guess I've got no choice, huh?
You guys can't be trusted on your own,
so I'll join your guild to keep an eye on you.
You'd better show me some gratitude.
Thank you, Karyl!
Hey! Quit hugging me!
Time to get this show on the road!
Our guild's objective
is to investigate and seek out every kind of
cuisine and ingredient to be found in the world!
And then to enjoy eating them together!
We'll call it the Gourmet Guild!
Let's get this party started!
Right here, right now!
Welcome!