Looks like someone's been making their move.
You mean her?
Well, time will continue to march on.
Our enemy won't loiter around forever.
It's in your hands now.
Your Majesty...
It's morning, everybody!
Your suepr yummy breakfast is ready!
Lady Karyl is awfully late.
Sleepyhead.
We can't have that!
Her yummy breakfast will get cold!
Good morning, Karyl!
Breakfast is getting cold!
Karyl! Karyl!
Karyl? Karyl?!
E-Emergency, Kokkoro!
Karyl isn't answering!
What if she's fallen and can't get up?!
Hey! What gave you that stupid idea, Dumborine?!
I just want to slee—
Are you okay, Karyl?!
Oh...
Learn to control yourself!
You need to be more respectful
of people's personal space.
Perfonahl?
What's that? Sounds tasty!
Not something for you to eat!
I believe she means you need to learn
how to keep your distance from others.
I'm sorry. I'll try to be more thoughtful.
Are you sure you get it?
That aside, what are you gonna do
about my favourite plushie?
All torn up.
Um, if you'd like, I could fix it.
You can?
I did a lot of sewing work back home.
That's our Kokkoro!
Nice.
You really shine at times like these, Korosuke!
Thank you.
We'll be off now.
See you later!
You'd better take good care of him!
Well, guess I'll tidy my room.
First we must look for material
that matches the plushie's colour.
Mhm!
There are so many lovely shops.
My heart can't help but skip a beat.
Did you finish the shoes I ordered?
Sure did. Just a moment, please.
What?
Wait. Who made those shoes, anyway?
I can't make them.
Hey, what's the hold-up?
You going senile already?
It's harder to find a fabric store than I expected.
I'm sure there must be some in a town this big.
I'll look there.
I get it!
It'll be more efficient if we split up!
Mhm.
I'm worried that my lord might get lost.
It's okay.
Okay.
Material...
Sacred Punish!
It's a good thing I came.
I can't believe they'd show up here, too.
Um, thank—
I've missed you, my dearest little brother!
You're not hurt, are you? Were you scared?
Is your tummy okay?
You always got tummy-aches
whenever you were nervous.
Are you okay? Should I take you to the bathroom?
Can you pull your pants down by yourself?
Oh, that's right. You've lost your memories.
Don't worry. Your big sister's right here with you.
Big... sister?
Hey!
You shouldn't be out here, Shizuru!
Did you forget what our master told us?
We're supposed to watch from afar, remember?!
Sure, but...
Enough of that! Go!
Sorry about her!
No matter what happens, I'll watch over you!
I'll be watching over you!
I'll always be watching over you!
Who was that?
No fair, Sis! You can't just get a head start on me!
Sorry, Rino. I was just so happy,
I couldn't stop myself.
I want to talk with my brother so much, too!
About this and that, and all that, too!
There's so much I want to ask him about!
Y'know what, I'm gonna go see him right now!
You need to calm... down!
down!
Down!
Wh-What was I doing?!
Calm down, Rino.
Remember what our goal is?
That's right! To watch over
our dear brother from the sidelines!
Yes, exactly.
So let's do just that.
Aye, aye!
Wait, hold up. What was I doing a minute ago?
I can't remember.
Perfecto!
I should go report to Her Majesty.
I just can't find a single one at all.
How beautiful.
Where could it fluttered off to?
Darn it all.
I can't believe Dumborine did such
a number on my favourite plushie.
Can Kokkoro really fix it?
They're so pretty!
Oh, I know!
Her Majesty's always holed up in her castle.
I bet she'll be happy to see some pretty flowers.
Yeah, Shadows have begun showing up in town now.
Good thing we decided to make our move early.
I've relayed their coördinates.
Thanks. I see them.
There's a lot more than I realised.
Stay on your toes.
Understood, Master.
My lord!
How'd it go? Did you find any material?
Nope.
I see.
If we can't find any, I guess we must simply
become apprentices to a dyer.
I believe that if anyone could pull that off,
it would be you, Lady Pecorine.
In any case, let's keep looking around
a little longer for Lady Karyl's sake.
Yeah!
Your Majesty!
Look at these flowers!
Your Majesty?
Where is she?
Come here, Karyl.
I will show you something wonderful.
What do you think of this persona?
Isn't it beautiful?
Now, go.
Bring back an even finer drink for me.
What is that filth?
This is a sacred place.
Discard it at once.
Of course.
I don't see any.
Hey, you two! Stop for a bite! Food's good here!
Many thanks!
The hint of spicy flavour suits the meat well.
My lord, your mouth is a mess.
And here, too.
That will most likely stain.
I'll go to soak my handkerchief in some water.
This is perfect.
Koro?
Hold it right there!
Hoold it right there!
Hoooold it right there!
Hooooold it right there!
Hoooooold it right there!
Hooooooold it right there!
Hoooooooold it right there!
Hooooooooold it right there!
Hoooooooooold it right there!
Hooooooooooold it right there!
Hoooooooooooold it right there!
Hooooooooooooold it right there!
Hoooooooooooooold it right there!
Hooooooooooooooold it right there!
Hoooooooooooooooold it right there!
What do you think you're doing to my brother?!
Huh? Um, who might you be?
Don't answer my question with another question!
Eep!
I-I'm very sorry.
My name is Kokkoro, and I serve my lord.
Serve?
I serve him by order of the great Lady Ameth.
You serve him?! You not his girlfriend or anythin'?!
What's going on, Rino?
Bad news, Shizuru!
This strange girl is hanging around our brother!
She showed up out of nowhere!
Who does she think she is?!
You need to calm... down!
down!
Eep!
I'm sorry.
She tends to get a bit worked up
because our brother is very dear to us.
I'm Shizuru, and this is Rino.
Hi...
I-It's all right.
I'm Rino...
My name is Kokkoro.
What an auspicious day this is...
Um, I wasn't aware that my lord had sisters.
That's right.
Rino and I are his...
Oh, look, birdies...
Wait! He's gone!
My lord...
Did the Shadows get him?
In the middle of the city?
People have been going missing in Landosol.
We refer to them as the Lost.
I'm worried.
We should split up and search for him!
Right.
Lady Pecorine!
What's wrong, Kokkoro(**-chan}?
Did you find the material?
No, but that's not the issue.
My lord has gone missing.
What?!
A bystander I ran into said the Shadows
have started appearing in Landosol, too.
Here, in the middle of town?!
I can't be sure that's what happened,
but we couldn't find any clues...
You think that boy from before is okay?
He sure caught the attention of some dicey folk.
Good luck to him.
Excuse me!
Could you please tell us more about that?
Whoa... Wh-Where'd you come from?
Oh, was that boy a friend of yours?
You poor girls.
You don't know who you're dealing with.
Best give up on him.
He's very dear to me!
No matter what happened, I'll save him!
So this is the place?
My lord... I'm coming to save you now.
The hell?!
A raid?!
My lord, are you all right?!
All right! Give Yuuki back!
Peco lady!
Eep!
Ch-Charlie?!
You came to save me!
I saw a cute girl, so I couldn't resist making a pass,
but then I got kidnapped!
Awfully noisy out here.
Who's the dumbass with the death wish?
This here is the gate to Hell!
Whump.
You have the gall to defy me?!
I'll ram my hands right into your earholes and
make your bellybutton lint do the monkey dance!
Oh.
Uh, hey! Sorry 'bout all the fuss!
We're sorry!
Oh, there's a lotta dog shit
around here, so watch your step!
Oh, crap! I just stepped in it!
Thank you!
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
Rino!
I won't miss!
Arrow Rain!
This isn't the place.
Yuuki...
Miss Shizuru! Miss Rino!
Who's this?
This is my guildmate, Lady Pecorine.
You two are looking for Yuuki, right?
Thank you.
Kokkoro, have you found any clues?
No.
We have no other choice.
We should post a request for a search.
Oh? What's the matter?
Well, my lord has gone missing.
If you mean Yuuki, he was here earlier today.
Was he really?!
Welcome back, Yuuki.
I'm back.
Here you go.
What a perfect rainbow silkworm.
That completes your quest.
Um... What is this?
He said he was looking for
some kind of rare material,
and he asked me if I had any good quests.
You went by yourself?
Mhm!
When we were eating hot dogs...
It looked like I'd be able to
get the material we were looking for,
so I accepted the quest.
You did such a difficult quest by yourself.
I'm so glad you're safe.
It almost ate me!
Thank you so much, Yuuki!
Do you think we can fix Karyl's plushie now?
Yes!
He may have lost his memories,
but his selflessness is still in tact.
He's still the same old brother we love.
Miss Shizuru, Miss Rino, thank you for—
Truly, thank you both so much.
That Shadow was way different from the others.
Should I really continue this?
I'm home! And I'm starving...
We're home!
We have returned.
Took you long enough!
What crazy detours did you make this time?
Hi there.
Long time no see.
Never thought chasing those Shadows
would lead me to you.
Have you been looking into Omniscient Kaiser, too?
C'mon, don't get so defensive.
I bear no grudges toward you.
I don't have enough information
to trust that statement,
Queen Labyrinth.
It's been a long time since someone called me that,
Metamorregnant.
I have no interest in joining forces right now.
See you again sometime,
fellow Seven Crown.