Sorry, lad! That one's not quite a winner.
Have a piece of candy as a consolation.
Okay, who's next?
There's nothing like the bustling city of Landosol.
Where else can I take part in a lottery
with coupons I got for free by shopping?
I bet those shoes
would look fantastic on my lord.
Okay, young lady. It's your turn now.
Y-Yes.
Here you are.
All right.
You get four spins.
That's a poor streak, but you still got
one spin left to go, young lady!
I-Indeed...
Great Lady Ameth, please lend me strength.
I worked up a good sweat again today.
I've actually grown rather attached to them.
Not surprising given how much effort I've put in.
Who am I, Pecorine?
Darn it! I'm hungry!
I'm home...
Is dinner ready?
Welcome home.
Listen to this, Karyl!
Kokkoro won first prize in a lottery!
We're going to the beach! The beach!
The beach?!
My lord, could you spare me a moment of your time?
Sure.
Thank you.
U-Um...
I'm sure you're wondering why I'm dressed like this.
Since I grew up in the forest,
the concept of swimsuits was foreign to me.
I-I don't know if this one suits me,
and I... um... feel a bit anxious about it...
So I've come to show it off.
D-Does it look all right on me?
I can't be sure by myself.
The people in the store complimented me,
saying it was very cute...
But if it isn't to your liking,
then their compliments mean little to me.
Mhm!
Y-You really mean it?
I'm happy I got that off my chest.
Also...
I borrowed this instructional book
on how to swim from the library.
Am I doing it right?
Ooh.
You are very industrious, my lord.
Mhm!
In that case, allow me to train with you.
Pipe down, guys! I can't sleep with all that noise!
Yahoo!
Lookie at that, it's the ocean!
Crazy, ain't it?
Thank you, Kokkoro!
I'm happy to see you're enjoying it.
There you are, Karyl!
Now, now! Don't just hide in the back!
H-Hey!
S-Stop looking at me! Don't make me kill you!
I never imagined we'd be hitting the beach
right after I was ordered to observe them!
Get good and wet!
My eyes! My eyes! My eyes!
Ocean water has salt in it.
My eyes! My eyes!
The best thing you can do is close your eyes.
Salty.
Salty!
M-My lord...
Now you've gone and done it, Yuuki!
If that's how you wanna play...
Princess Splash!
Am I on vacation with toddlers or something?
Karyl! Don't be shy, you can come swim with us!
Hey! Get off! Are you trying to drown me?
You can't swim?
N-No, I can't! If you get it, let go of me!
In that case, let me invite you on a cruise!
Huh?
The ship is now departing!
Don't!
At least stay somewhere I can reach the bottom!
This feels great!
Crazy, ain't it?
Lord, have mercy!
They appear to be having a good time.
Whew...
I wore myself out on the way back.
How crazy was that?
"How crazy was that", my foot!
Don't take the sea lightly!
How unusual.
You rarely get worn down, Lady Pecorine.
Actually, just between us...
The armour I usually wear
has all kinds of beneficial effects.
Stuff like improved physical strength,
enhanced nourishment, exhaustion recovery...
It even protects me stiff shoulders and the cold!
Really?
But in exchange, I get hungry way faster.
Isn't that crazy?
Armourless, I'm no different from your everyday girl!
I had no idea there was such
a secret to your strength and appetite.
H-Hang on! Are you sure you should
tell us something like that?
It's fine! We're all friends here.
S-Stop!
S-Stooooooooooooop!
M-Miss Suzume?!
Th-Thanks for saving me!
Are you all right, Miss Suzume?
Oh, Kokkoro! It's good to see you again!
Oh, you know each other?
Yes. This is the lady from the bazaar I mentioned.
Ah, so that's you.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Suzume of the Sarendia Orphanage.
Likewise. I'm Karyl.
Heya! I'm Pecorine!
Yuuki.
What are you delivering?
Well, we've actually started a beachside snack hut.
Oh, I know!
It's wonderful to see you again.
A pleasure to see you after so long, Miss Saren.
So, you three are Kokkoro's guildmates?
Pleasure to meet you.
This is a lovely establishment.
Thanks!
Have you decided what you'd like to order?
It all sounds delicious!
Everything from here to here!
All of it, please!
Thanks for the food!
You were right.
It really is a joy watching them eat.
By the way, I notice there's no one else here,
despite being lunchtime.
You're right. And the food's so good, too!
Truth be told, there's another snack hut on this beach,
and their featured menu item
drew away all our customers.
Don't worry!
I'll just come eat here every day!
That would blow the Gourmet Guild's entire budget!
Rein it in!
Exactly what is their featured item?
Well, you see...
Come one, come all!
Get your meowthwatering taiyaki right here, folks!
Three taiyaki!
I want seven!
Eight with white bean paste, please!
You got it!
No purrshing, meow!
We'll bake up enough furresh,
tasty taiyaki for all of you!
Please enter the line here!
Oh, wow...
I hate to admit it,
but Tamaki's taiyaki tastes really good.
Perhaps, but who wants piping-hot taiyaki
in this blistering heat?
That's the problem with you novices.
You must always think outside the box
for any and all potential business opportunities.
N-Novices? Who does this woman think she is?
That's Miss Akino,
president of the Mercurius Foundation.
Are you per chance new to Saren's snack hut?
Good day.
Snap!
You want something cold to eat in this heat?
Nonsense! That's a preconception!
A nice, warm, sugary refreshment is just
what you need when you're chilled from the ocean!
Hence, taiyaki!
You absolute novice!
Once again, good day!
I hope you have prepared a favourable
answer for me today, Saren.
Not one to give up, are you?
We have no intention of working under you.
You certainly play hard to get.
If you keep this up, you'll find yourself in debt.
Just cave in and become my business partner.
Akino recognises and values your talent, Saren.
Sorry she's so tactless about it.
Hey! Mifuyu!
Thank you, I'm well aware.
She's been like this since way back.
Saren!
A-Anyway!
Summer won't wait forever!
You'd better come work for me
before summer ends and you lose your chance!
Or do you think you can make something
even better than Tamaki's taiyaki?
Well, I suppose that would be
too tall an order for a bunch of novices.
The audacity of that woman!
Listen up. The Gourmet Guild is to help
come up with a new featured menu item.
I won't just twiddle my thumbs
as she walks all over us!
Akino's parents run a major conglomerate.
She's been going on about how she wants to
be a successful merchant without their help,
so she founded the Mercurius Foundation.
That's why she's so motivated.
She's a good girl at heart.
We appreciate that the
Gourmet Guild is offering to help,
but we wouldn't want to take away
from your precious holiday time.
We very much enjoy coming up with new dishes!
That's true.
The Gourmet Guild's mission
is to study delicious foods.
You can leave everything in our capable hands!
Ingredients...
Ready, Suzume? Here I go!
Okay!
And... hup!
Are you okay, Suzume?
I'm sorry, milady.
It's a lot better to be out working
than be inside worrying sick, huh?
It sure is!
Look at this, my lord.
If this has a good flavour,
it could make for an interesting ingre—
Noodles came out.
Akino! It's cat nap time!
Nothing beats taiyaki after a hard day's work.
I can't think of anything that hits the spot
as well as a good, strong drink does.
Wh-Who gave Yukari booze?!
Come on, it's still bright out!
What's gotten into you?!
Meow?
Akino suddenly wanted to start a new business
on the beach, so I offered to help her...
But day in, day out, I'm surrounded by nothing but
lovey-dovey couples as far as the eye can see...
Look that way, and there's a couple!
Look this way, and there's a couple!
This will be the end of me without some alcohol!
Huh?!
I want someone to take me with them for takeout!
I'd like that to go, please.
Who just got ordered to go?!
Meow, take it easy!
It's just a customer ordering taiyaki to go!
Fine! I'll just drink!
You're gonna damage the snack hut
if you don't knock it off!
Yukari, you need to cool your head!
Oh, gosh! Tamaki's takin' me out!
No, I'm not!
Don't say junk that'll give people funny ideas!
Why'd you bring me to this place
where we're all alone, oh gosh, you?
Sheesh, how about we snap the
usually-cool-as-a-cucumber Tamaki back to her senses?
Hi-yah!
It's shallow?
Is she stuck in the sand?
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow!
What a great catch!
I know! Why don't we make ice sushi?
Ice sushi?
We'll replace rice with ice and put sashimi on it!
Rejected.
How about a stewed fish dish
made with coconut milk?
Hmm... Lacks punch, I'd say.
If I may...
I believe this offers quite a punch.
I mean, yes, but it also kinda kills my appetite.
Does it?
It's the Kraken!
Come to your senses already, you drunkard!
Tamaki! What's going on?
Saren! It's Yukari!
Yukari?!
I threw her in the water to sober her up,
and that huge squid showed up!
You're not allowed to swim here
because that Kraken lives in these waters!
S-Say what?!
It's takin' me out!
Y-Yukari!
Stop! Wait right there!
Pecorine?!
Lady Pecorine!
Don't take her out into deep water!
Takin' me out!
She stopped that Kraken by herself?
I swear, it's been nothing but endless trouble
ever since I joined this guild.
Yes...
But when I lived back home, I never dreamed
that life could be so exciting.
Well, I prefer life nice and quiet!
Pecorine, we're blowing that thing sky-high!
Okay, Karyl!
Here goes nothing!
Grim Burst!
Nice one, Karyl!
Leave the rest to me!
Sword of Phoenix!
Thanks so much! You saved the day!
Take care.
I'm glad everyone's all right.
What should we do with this Kraken?
Yes, your grilled Kraken is ready!
Five squid ink ice creams, please!
Coming right up!
I can't believe it.
I never expected you to serve
the legendary Kraken as a dish.
Packs quite a punch, wouldn't you say?
And it was the novice who came up with the idea.
Well, you certainly showed me.
From now on, I'll listen to what
novices have to say, too.
I've always liked how flexible you can be.
Hey! Would you stop that?!
Still, I guess now we can discuss business as equals.
I appreciate that you asked me to work
for you out of concern,
but I always want to be on equal footing with you.
Saren...
I bet we could put squid ink
ice cream and taiyaki together
to make the ultimate dessert.
You amaze me.
But that's to be expected of someone
befitting to be my rival.
Come on, stand in line!
It's thanks to Korosuke that we came to the beach
and came up with a new specialty.
So, this is my reward for you.
N-Nothing has changed...
Wouldn't you love to swim freely under the sea?
It looks just like the Dragon King's Palace...
It's as if we've all turned into fish.
Everything is so vivid and gorgeous.
I must thank Lady Karyl for using this spell on us.
My lord,
I've always had a vision.
A vision of a vast universe
that expands far beyond the skies above.
Of great seas many times more vast than the land.
Of mysteries from all across the globe
left unfound deep within the mountains.
Of different countries home to people
beyond those I know.
I always soothed my soul by imagining
these things whenever I felt lonely.
But ever since I met you, my lord,
I've seen far, far grander sights
than I had ever dreamed of before.
So...
You may not understand why I would say this, but...
Thank you, my lord.