My lord, my heart breaks for you...
Bathtime was fun.
That's what you get for not drying your hair properly.
What are you, a little kid?
Okay, here's some piping-hot rice porridge.
It'll warm you up and make you feel
a hundred times more energetic!
Was it too hot?
But you need to eat lots and lots
if you wanna feel better.
Open wide!
You're spoiling him too much.
He's a man, right? He'll toughen it out
after a good night's rest.
Y-Your face is a bit red...
You're burning up!
H-Hey, I think he's in serious trouble!
I'm preparing the fever medicine
we use back in my hometown.
Now hold the hell up!
Why are you throwing in bugs so nonchalantly?
Well, in the town I grew up in...
Spare us your silly bumpkin remedies!
Hey, you! Exactly what do you think
you're sticking in that porridge?!
What? But it's full of nutrients...
Why do you guys think bugs are some miracle cure?!
Guess it's all up to me now!
I'm dragging his ass to an actual hospital!
Is it this way?
Give me a second.
It's not like I go to the hospital often.
Let's see...
Oh, looks like it's this way.
Let's take a look.
Excuse me! We have an emergency patient!
Of course! What appears to be the problem?
Um... This is the hospital, right?
Yep, it sure is!
He's had a fever since last night.
Oh, my... What have we here?
Yeet him to the examination room!
Open wide, now.
That's a good boy.
The doctor and nurse dress a little funny,
but it seems they can give him a proper exam.
Karyl, judging people by their appearance is a no-no.
You're asking too much of me here.
You've gotta have a screw lose if you're
not even a little concerned by those outfits.
Now, take off your shirt
and let me see your belly.
Quiet down, you two.
You're packing quite some muscle
in such a slender body.
Oh?
This looks like...
It definitely is.
Indeed.
Nanaka, prepare to operate!
Yes, Doctor!
What?!
D-Doctor, is he all right?!
Silence, gawkers!
I'll make him feel a whole thirty percent better!
Let's begin.
I-Isn't this much more serious than we thought?!
Th-They do say that colds can lead to worse illnesses...
Arattama, kiyottama...
Great Lady Ameth, grant my lord strength!
C-Cut it out!
Arattama, kiyottama...
Kokkoro, calm down!
Arattama, kiyottama...  Arattama, kiyo—
Keep it together, Kokkoro!
This is a hospital, for crying out loud!
I-I'm sorry. I couldn't stand idly by.
All sense of reason goes straight out the window
when it comes to him, huh?
Be more careful.
This is a Landosol clinic.
There's nothing to worry about.
Okay...
M-My lord... My lord is...
Hey! Get a grip!
Stay with us, Kokkoro!
I-I'm so sorry!
Quit cloggin' up the hallway, you—
I-It's you guys!
Wait, aren't you that guy?
The guy who barged into
the Cockatrice's Nest to complain!
It's so good!
You're a lot skinnier now.
Have you been eating properly?
Cut the crap! It's all your fault that I...
Th-They're operating right now, right?
Yes.
This is my only chance!
If I let it slip by,
I'll never break free from this hell!
Huh? Um, what does that—
This ain't no hospital!
It's a prison!
Sorry, but I'm gettin' the hell outta here
while those maniacs aren't around!
The hell was that?! The hell did he mean?!
Why was he panicking so much?
I-It might not be too late
to go to a different hospital.
G-Good idea!
It might be rude to the doctor,
but with the state that guy is i—
Oh mah lawd!
Hee, hee, hee...
You're quite the ill-mannered patient, aren't you?
Let's return you to your bed.
I can't waste too much time on you.
I have to find my soulmate.
Hee, hee, hee, hee...
Hee, hee, hee, hee, hee, hee...
E-Excuse me! What sort of disease does he have?!
Kokkoro?!
You guys should skedaddle on outta here.
I never saw any of that coming.
It's been nothing but trouble
ever since we started the guild.
Hey, Korosuke, we don't need you
collapsing on us too, now.
She's right, Kokkoro.
At times like these, it's important to enjoy
a hearty meal and build up energy!
Right.
I'll have the owner cook up
his secret menu right away!
Stop. Get us normal food.
But it'd give us energy.
Karyl, you're oh-so-selfish!
Acting all cutesy won't make me change my mind!
Oh, Eriko, did you grab
the drug made of mandrake?
It smelled so nice, I couldn't resist.
You shouldn't have. That stuff is poison.
I know. It knocked me out not long ago.
Don't touch things on the
medicine shelf without permission.
Hee, hee...
Ah, how I wish I knew
where my soulmate was right now...
I know we'll meet again one day.
We're tied by the red thread of fate!
Hee, hee, hee, hee...
Excuse me.
Would you care to have your fortune told?
It's free of charge.
My father is quite eager to tell your fortune.
Welcome.
Now, then...
What a lovely knick-knack.
Hi, young lady! Care to have a drink with me?
I very much do not appreciate this kind of humour.
Dad, you're a bit too direct.
S-Sorry! I was just joking around!
Hey, Shinobu! You say something!
It'd do you well to suffer a bit
every now and then, dad.
Shinobu!
This was a waste of my time. Say your prayers.
W-Wait a second! I've read your fortune!
You're looking for your soulmate, right?
Soon! You'll see him soon!
Your soulmate will soon appear
before you with a warm sigh!
I'll see him soon...
Hey, girlie! Let's drink! Come drink with me!
Not him.
Five seconds! Five seconds is all I need!
I finally found you! My Cinderella!
Not him.
None of you are fit.
He's my soulmate. No one else.
I didn't see him today either.
Hee, hee, hee...
Found you.
Morning.
Heya!
Good morning, Lady Karyl.
I hope Yuuki is feeling better today.
I have my doubts. That doctor seemed
a bit too eccentric. The nurse, too.
Why don't we go check up on him after breakfast?
Okay.
For all we know, he might already be
out of bed, craving food!
Hee, hee, hee...
Come, eat up.
Um... Can't.
Hee, hee, hee...
The secret ingredient is...
my... love... for... you.
Hurry!
Hold up! Why are we running out of the blue?
I just remembered a guild
that's brought up often in town!
Wh-What sort of guild?
W-Well...
Hey, you! Beat it!
What could possibly be the reason
you fine gentleman gathered here this morning?
Don't give us that crap!
You swiped the treasure
we stole off that rich jerk!
You've got some nerve,
stealing from thieves!
Nanaka, do you know what this is about?
I got no interest in people from
that side of town, so that's a nope!
Don't play dumb!
We know you're hiding that punk here! Don't we?!
Yeah!
You are much too noisy this early in the morning.
My beloved can't rest well
with such a racket, so...
Buzz off, insects.
See?! She's right there!
Eriko, do you know these people?
Let's not resort to fighting.
We're all friends here, aren't we?
Like hell we are!
Have you got a screw loose?!
Enough talk! Get her!
I see...
I take it you've said your prayers, then.
Deadly Punish!
Th-That move! Is she...
What?! What about it?!
We're in trouble! She's...
Hee, hee, hee, hee, hee...
The Destroyer!
My turn!
Have a taste of this!
Nanaka Infinite Presto!
YOLO!
Is she... the Collector?!
Whoa, that really sent 'em packing!
I only just learned that spell not long ago,
but I guess it blew you away, ey?
You're causing a disturbance, you two.
D-Don't tell me she's...
Curse Bloom!
My... My body is...
It really is her! The One-Eyed Devil!
You guys are the Twilight Caravan!
Oh, you've heard of our guild?
Hmm... We could just leave them like this,
but that'd be a pain in the neck.
I wouldn't mind bringing
them in for exams, though.
Incidentally, without the proper treatment,
you may very well just die out here.
P-Please, cure me! Right now!
Me, too!
Fix me up, too!
Help me!
Oh, dear. I'm going to have my hands full...
with all the new guinea pigs.
Let's go save him!
Yeah. This place is bad news.
Now that we have a plan,
let's carry it out right away!
Operation: Rescue Yuuki!
Nanaka, I need morphine over here!
Wrap green onions around that kraken!
Righto! Up, up, and away I go!
I'm so glad I get to test out
the new drug I've been saving.
It looks like we can make this work.
My lord, I'm coming to save—
Hee, hee, hee...
I hope you weren't scared
by those strange people outside.
The most dangerous-looking one is right there!
Oh, yes. I received something nice
from my friends who stopped by earlier.
I'm sure you'll love it.
See?
A cursed engagement ring.
They say couples that exchange
this ring are blessed by its curse,
allowing them to stay together forever and ever.
Eternally...
Wh-What do we do?! What do we do?!
His illness is the least of our concerns now!
I-If it's come to this...
Slow down, Korosuke!
If we make too much noise,
the doctor and her nurse will come running!
Yes, but...
Listen. You're the key.
Come...
Let us exchange our eternal vows.
Hee, hee, hee, hee, hee...
Something stinks.
Great Lady Ameth, lend me your strength!
What could Mitsuki and Nanaka be up to?
Doc! The patients are foaming at the mouth
and busting out some sick moves!
Okay, that's the expected reaction!
Relax! 'Tis but a flesh wound!
I can't let this go unchecked.
You can stay here and rest.
Yuuki!
You're okay, right?!
Let's make a break for it while we can!
This is the source.
What is that?
Do you think Kokkoro got away safely?
Don't worry. Korosuke can do anything
when she puts her mind to it.
Nanaka, there's a drug I'd like to try.
Keep an eye on things here.
Righto! You got it!
Experiments...
Can't wait to do my ex-pe-ri-ments.
Wh-What do we do?!
We have to go back up for now!
Someone's up there, too?!
There's nowhere to go!
If we're caught now,
no excuse is going to work!
What can we...
Ah, so much to do, so much to do!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
I-It suddenly hurts so much!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Oh, dear!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
What's wrong? Does your stomach hurt?
Let me see.
That's it. You can lean on the wall.
Ow, ow...
My lord!
Now, to continue where I left off with my love...
Are you all right?!
Karyl!
Let's see...
Can you show me where it hurts?
Oh, young folk have such tender skin!
What about here?
Does it hurt here? Or here?
Oh?
A new patient?
That's right!
We so rarely have young girls as patients here!
I'm so excited!
Oh! I'm better! I'm all better!
It doesn't hurt anymore. Whoa!
Doctor, the pain is all gone now!
Where are you taking me? Wait... No!
No!
Oh, my... This is...
Simply rest for a few days
and you'll feel good as new.
Look.
See this little rash here?
The symptoms resemble those of a cold,
so it's often misdiagnosed,
but this has already been treated.
And remarkably well at that!
Where did you have this examined prior?
A-Actually, we took him to Doctor Mitsuki.
Ah, I see.
That one is a bit... eccentric.
But her skills are the real deal,
so you've got nothing to worry about.
W-Well, a lot has happened,
but I guess we don't need to worry
about you being sick.
I'm glad.
I was... almost cursed.
From what that doctor said,
everyone who goes to Doctor Mitsuki's clinic
feels thirty percent better when they are discharged.
So let's pick up Karyl when she gets discharged tomorrow,
and hopefully she'll feel thirty percent better.
No worries!