Home at last!
Karyl!
You really did come back
feeling thirty percent better!
I'm so glad!
Nap time!
G-Goodnight...
Rise and shine!
I'm done preparing another delicious breakfast!
Good morning, Lady Pecorine.
Heya, you two!
You're all so loud in the morning.
Huh? When'd I get back here?
Come, come! Hurry up and take a seat.
Thank you for preparing breakfast.
Anytime!
I also made plans for us today!
You sure are full of pep
first thing in the morning.
Well, since you came back home
feeling thirty percent better,
I figured it was about time for our
Gourmet Guild to get the show on the road!
God, no. Please, don't remind me!
Never mention anything
concerning that clinic ever again!
S-Steamed buns a-are terrifying...
Ta-dah!
I went to look at the bulletin board
and found this request!
What is it?
"Recruiting help to harvest
raw spices in Targum."
"Your reward will be daily payments
plus a full set of spices."
Precisely!
This village's local speciality, Targum seed,
is so prized that it's known as the legendary spice!
I see. So this job will be a windfall,
like killing two birds with one stone.
Yes!
Physical labour just isn't for me,
speaking as a mage.
Count me out.
Sniffle, sniffle...
I-I wanted this to be o-our first guild quest...
together...
Okay, have it your way!
If that's what makes you happy, so be it!
Okay! Did all of you pack in your snacks?
Time to head out!
Yeah!
You really pulled out the crocodile tears, huh?
I don't like this.
Something's odd.
'Tis scary here.
I don't like this.
Something's odd.
'Tis scary here.
We haven't camped out since
the first few days, have we, my lord?
Campfire! Exciting!
Not even a nibble...
Who knows what they'll end up making
supper out of if I don't catch anything?
I need to catch something!
There's a bite! A bite! Bite! Bite! Bite!
Oh, these bugs look delicious.
Not so fast, Korosuke!
I'm this close to catching us some delicious fish!
Leave those bugs where they are!
This is rubbish. That lake is empty.
Don't worry.
We can make a soup from these wild plants
and the frogs my lord caught.
Spare me!
I don't want to eat frogs on the first night of our quest!
Now, don't say that. Look.
I caught lots!
Please, no! Just the vegetables is good enough!
I don't need more than that!
I'm back!
I caught a tasty-looking bird!
Welcome back.
Well done!
You're more on the ball today than ever before!
How long will it still take?
I'm starving.
You shouldn't rush these things, Karyl.
Just hold out a little longer.
Lady Pecorine, the soup is ready.
Thanks, Kokkoro!
Hey, why not cook it over their fire?
Non, non.
Do that and this exquisite meat will burn.
Steaming it over hot coals
will make it plump and juicy all the way through!
And the umami it produces will be to die for!
Gulp...
It's done!
Okay, I'm gonna open it up!
Ta-dah!
It smells divine!
Okay, everyone. The wait is over!
Dig in!
Yummy!
Can poultry really be this juicy?
I've never had any like this!
The vegetables you steamed with it
make it taste even sweeter.
Right?
I learned how to do this on my travels.
The best meals really do call for proper ingredients!
That means no bugs and frogs.
Am I clear, Korosuke?
What's that thing?
Oh, it's fruit I brought back along with the bird.
Go ahead and try some too, Karyl and Yuuki.
Wow, it smells so sweet!
They're very ripe!
Sweet!
Give me another!
There's plenty to go around.
No need to hold back!
This is the first time I've seen this fruit,
but it's a good thing I plucked some anyway!
Korosuke!
Yer way too uptight for such za li'l brat, I swear!
Wh-What's the matter with you, Lady Karyl?
I... I wyas supposed ta be
mjore responsible for her sake, thoo!
You there!
Kids who cry and eat loads grow up strong!
Now, don't hold back!
Cry to your heart's content!
There, there. You're such a good girl.
Bash, smash, crash!
Here comes the sesame miso! Crash!
Oi!
Come sing along with us, Kokkoro!
The tea jar enters and all the doors. Slam. Shut!
Oi...
Once it passes through, we can crash and bash!
Oi!
The mouse in the rice sack
eats the rice with a squeak!
Oi!
They're all wonderful people.
I'm so glad we started our guild.
Huh? What did I do again last night?
Morning, Karyl!
Lovely morning, isn't it?
I-Is it?
My head feels all fuzzy.
Good morning, Lady Karyl.
Here you go. You'll feel better
once you wash your face.
You're right.
My lord is washing his face by the lake right—
H-He crashed into it head-first!
This is exactly why I told you
to wait until they closed in on us!
A-Are you hurt?
I-I wasn't sure if I should i-interfere,
but it l-looked like you were
being ch-chased by a monster.
Don't do that! Be gentle with her!
Thank you.
Y-You're welcome!
Um... My name is Aoi!
I'm Yuuki.
It talks?
I-I'm not insane or anything!
I was just talking with my friend!
I carved her so I could practise
in case I ever made a real friend...
I call her "You Got This! Friend #1".
Friend?
I can speak with plants and animals,
but I don't have a single human friend.
I've always, always, always
wanted to become friends with a human.
I've wanted one for years.
My only conversation partner the entire time
has been You Got This! Friend #1...
But obviously we ran out of things
to talk about eventually.
I know for a fact I'm not ready to have
any real friends. Not by a long, long shot.
Friend?
Frie...nd?
Are you saying you're looking for a friend, too?!
I can't believe it! The last thing I expected
was to run into a fellow lonely soul today!
D-Don't worry, Yuuki!
Let's embark on this
friend-making quest together!
I'll have your back and we can make friends! Together!
We're a team from now on! Hooray!
Oh, right. We're a team.
And a team needs a team name!
Do you have any good ideas for a name,
You Got This! Friend #1?
Well, let's see...
This might be your big break from loneliness,
so you'll want to go all out.
Right? I can finally say farewell to my lonely times!
I know! How's "Team B-B" sound?
"Team B-B"?
You heard that right. "B-B" as in "Bye-Bye".
Say goodbye to your loneliness!
I love it! "Bye-Bye Loneliness" is perfect!
Team B-B! Team B-B!
Come on, Yuuki! Join me!
Team B-B! Team—
My lord!
Yuuki! Are you okay?
You appear to be unharmed.
You gave us a real fright there, y'know!
Oh? Who's this?
Aoi. She saved me.
I see.
Thank you very much for saving my lord.
Y-You're welcome.
Why are you walking so far behind us?
I-I wouldn't dare walk between
you guys when we're not even friends!
My name is Aoi, not Rudy McRudy!
Rather, how exactly are you gonna guide us
if we're the ones walking in front?
I'm glad you were also headed to Targum for the harvest!
P-Please!
Guiding you there is the least
a lonely soul like me could do!
I can see the village.
That's it, right?
Welcome to Targum.
We came in response to the request.
What's the name of your guild?
W-We're, um...
I've got this!
We're the Gourmet Guild!
I'm Misato of Forestier.
There's currently another girl named Hatsune
staying in this village too aside from Aoi here,
but she appears to be off napping somewhere.
We don't have enough people to harvest our rich crop
this year, so we appreciate any help we can get.
There's another group called Elizabeth Park
that was supposed to come help today, too.
Elizabeth Park?
What about it?
Someone who helped me a while ago was in that guild.
Oh, an acquaintance?
Yes.
A lovely girl named Rima.
Rima, rima, rima! Rima, rima!
Hey, slow down a little!
Rima?
Sorry! I'm just so excited for the harvest.
You're leaving Shiorin in the dust.
I'm all right...
I know we have to get there...
by the end of the day...
Shio-shio, dontcha push yourself too hard, now.
Not even ta see your big sis.
Ya don't wanna make it worse, do ya?
How's a breather sound?
I'm in!
Shiorin...
Nothing's more comfy than a fluffy bed.
I'm not a bed! I'm a beautiful lady!
But you're welcome to rest on me, Shiori.
It'll perk you right up.
Thank you.
Everyone loves you 'cause
you're such a beaut, Rima-rima.
O-Oh gosh! Me? A beauty?!
Ptoo!
Maybe it's because I did up my bangs today?
Slow... down. Slow down a little.
Don't... push yourself... too hard.
What's going on?
It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
Slow down...
Slow down. Slow down. Slow down.
Th-They're so scary!
Stay away from us, darn it!
Fluffy Strike!
Fluffy Strike.
It knows the same move?
It's such a nice, peaceful village.
Indeed.
You think so?
I'm a city girl, so it's pretty lame out here if you ask me.
Isn't there anything... fun... to do...?
The hell?
A girl is floating in the air!
Should you really sound so delighted by that?!
She's still fast asleep.
Um...
Huh? How did I get here?
Are you all right?
You just fell from way up there.
What? Was I flying again?!
"Again"?
Oh, forget I said that!
I'm Hatsune!
I'm still a little sleepy, but I'm just a normal girl!
Hatsune? That Forestier member?
We gots to nail our timing, Shio-shio!
Okay, Mahiru!
Fork Slash!
Here we go!
Okay!
Double Hip Attack!
Nice one, Rin!
Same to you, Rima!
If we break through their vanguard, we got 'em!
I'm... all right...
I'm all right...
They can only say the same thing,
and their movements are clumsy.
I'm all right...
We will manage.
Looks like there's some fun event going on here.
Turns out my hunch was pretty much on point.
Greetings, you cute little beasts.
I am Christina.
Now, get on your feet.
You can still dance, can't you?
Please don't disappoint me.
Oh, you're here for the harvest, too?
We look forward to working with you.
Same here!
It looks like it's going to be a lot of fun!
I'm super excited!
I'll get to see my sister
for the first time in ages, too!
You have a sister?
Yeah! She's in Elizabeth Park.
She's been recovering from an illness,
and it seems she's feeling a bit better!
What were those things?
She's a real bookworm!
She's really frail, but gets so immersed.
She'll keep reading late into the night.
Hatsune...
I'm... all right...
We have to get there...
by the end of the day...
I'm... all right...
I bought her a new book,
and I can't wait to give it to her!
I bet it'd make her super happy!
Hatsune...
I'm... all... right...
Here comes the sesame miso! Crash!
Crash!