Sorry, did I wake you?
You can sleep a little longer.
I have to focus on this.
You must be wondering who I am.
That kinda upsets me, honestly.
We've been through so much together.
I'm...
Well, you can call me Ameth.
I can't interact with reality
until I'm done fixing myself up.
In light of that, I have assigned someone else
to serve as your guide in my stead.
I really wish we could chat a little longer,
but you can't keep dreaming forever.
What a pretty star!
Is it a shooting star?
Kokkoro.
You mustn't fail to carry out
the oracle of Lady Ameth.
Father,
I'll serve my lord to my utmost ability.
On the hills up ahead lies the land of prophecy.
I wonder what he's like.
I mustn't look sloppy in his presence.
That must be him.
He must be
my lord—
M-My lord!
Th-That was close.
First you simmer, simmer,
then boil up hot, hot.
Keep that rice snug...
Have you finally awoken, my lord?
Do you feel any pain?
I'm glad you seem to be in good health.
I was sent by the great Lady Ameth
to serve as your guide.
My name is Kokkoro.
It is my sworn duty to protect you,
from dawn to dusk,
from the cradle to the grave,
and to devote my entire being
to your service, my lord.
Oh my?
If it's okay with you, would you
be willing to share your name with me?
Yuuki.
My name is Yuuki.
I'm glad to hear that.
I am now certain you are the lord
I was meant to serve.
According to the oracle of Lady Ameth,
it would seem you have lost many of your memories.
I'm sure you must be quite confused.
But I am here to guide you,
so you can be at ease.
Please, have some.
It appears they have not given up.
My lord.
They will serve as the perfect
opponents for us right now.
By accumulating experience,
you will slowly regain your original abilities.
Any foe would be powerless before you.
And I shall brush away any sparks
that may rain upon you.
Now, let us engage!
M-My lord!
A-Are you all right, my lord?
Please forgive me.
I got ahead of myself and neglected
that you had only just awakened...
M-My lord!
Landosol's only another day away or so.
It's a downright shame
stone monsters are too hard to eat.
That should do the trick!
Father, Mother...
Help! Somebody, please! Help us!
Is something the matter?
Ouch, ouch, ouch! Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Bro! Hang in there, Bro!
The world is one, big blur.
Don't be ridiculous, Bro!
No! Whatever you do, don't close your eyes!
Did some monster attack you?
Oh, you came in the nick of time, young lady!
I can see a beautiful flower field...
My bro's chronic beriberi has taken a turn for
the worse, and now he's off his rocker!
Oh, my late grandma is waving at me...
Do you see that sack up there?
His medicine is in there!
Could you please fetch it for him?
It hurts... All I feel is pain...
Of course! The medicine, you said?
We're counting on you, cutie!
I got it!
Huh?
Wha-ha-ha—?
We hit the jackpot, Bro!
Much obliged!
Wha—?!
Wait! Please!
We've arrived.
I am truly relieved you weren't injured.
How about you join me for a bath?
A tail?
A bath?
I have some great soap.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
She is of the beast clan.
In this world there are humans, elves,
beasts, and demons, just to name a few.
Oh, you'll find that place on
the second corner down the road.
Do you think you'll be fine by yourself?
Incidentally, I am an elf.
Landosol, where we are right now,
is the largest nation on the continent of Astraea.
We are currently in its capital.
We got some fresh fish 'ere! Come take a look!
Oh, forgive me. It all seemed so curious to me.
Huh? My lord?
Come now! Step right up!
Welcome!
Oh? Brother and sister out shopping together?
How cute. What will it be?
I-I'm not his little sister...
Oh, you're not?
Girlfriend then, perhaps?
N-N-No, I'm not!
Sorry about that.
So, what kinda crêpe would you like?
Great!
Chocolate and strawberry, coming right up!
My lord, here you go.
My lord! You shouldn't put that in your mouth!
You can't eat that!
Spit it out! Spit!
Ptoo.
I forgot you had lost your memories.
This is money.
You can exchange it for various goods
and services from shops.
It's not meant to be eaten.
Was my explanation clear?
Thanks for the wait!
Wonderful! Now we're all set to go shopping!
Money. Important. Learned.
It's delicious.
This is the first time I've had something like this.
It's so sweet,
and the strawberry-flavoured sau—
Y-You have done well today.
I'll find lodging for us.
You can stay here and rest.
What?
I'm very sorry, young lady.
But I've got mouths to feed, y'know.
You're welcome anytime once you can afford it!
My sincerest apologies.
I didn't realise lodging was so expensive.
If it's come to this, I can pawn
the staff my father gave—
He hasn't complained once
about my lacklustre guidance.
Rather, he's been very accepting.
He is much too kind.
Tomorrow... for my lord, I will...
M-My lord!
Please forgive me!
I should have been more alert
while we were camping!
I fear that if this continues,
you'll end up as a wolf snack one day.
As such, I've decided to take precautions.
You should try to enjoy yourself while I'm busy.
You could eat out or find something else to do.
This is your allowance for the day.
Here you go.
I'll be back at fifth bell.
We can meet up again here.
What's wrong?
Is being in an unfamiliar environment making you ill?
Or is that amount of money perhaps insufficient?
My apologies. This is all the money we have.
I'll go sell some of my ornaments for mo—
My lord, what's the matter?
Money important.
Money important! Learned!
This must be the place.
But are you sure you wish to work?
What might bring you here?
I'm Karin, and I work for the Guild Association.
If there's anything I can do to help,
please don't hesitate to call me.
I heard there is a bulletin board here with job postings.
There is. I'll show you.
Let's see...
Subjugation quests, escort quests...
There's also dungeoneering.
I wouldn't recommend any of these to beginners.
"Reports of a dragon sighted in the vicinity of Landosol."
"Seeking members for a team to defeat the dragon"
"that has been attracted to Landosol's riches
and has led to casualties."
This does not sound like a quest we could handle.
Oh! This one should be suitable!
It's a fetch quest.
There's a request for someone to gather
some mushrooms that grow in the Gado Ruins.
It doesn't seem too dangerous.
I'd recommend this.
We accept!
I hope that poor man from yesterday is all right.
I've gotta hurry and give him his medicine.
I'm also concerned about the sword
Mother and Father gave me.
And I'm hungry as a wolf
after fending off all those monsters.
Yeah!
I'm Ikacchi!
You're Charlie!
It's the beriberi man from yesterday!
Are you all right now?
That chick just doesn't give up!
She still believes that obvious bullshit?!
Huh?
Come back! I have your medicine right here!
What you think?
I think the coast is clear.
Just a li'l bit till we're in Landosol, Bro!
Yeah!
And once we sell this thing,
we'll be rolling in dough!
This way, my lord.
Look closely.
They grow in places like this.
Try looking for some in similar spots.
This forest sure has a lot of mushrooms.
It must be a scarcely-known hotspot.
What an unusual mushroom.
Since you go "puchipuchi", I'm calling you Puchiko.
I know we need that quest reward,
but I can't take a tiny life like yours.
Hide in here, Puchiko.
M-My poor stomach...
Mhm-mmm!
Nothing gives you quite a boost like rice!
You really saved me and my tummy!
It was so kind of you to share
such delicious food with a total stranger!
I'm forever in your debt!
Excuse me, but what brings you out to these woods?
Oh, well... I've been travelling for
some personal reasons, y'see?
I thought I'd visit my homeland,
Landosol, for the first time in a while.
But whoopsie, I almost starved!
And you collapsed on the way there?
Sure did! How crazy is that?
What about you two?
We're here to gather mushrooms.
Those look delicious.
Feel free to have some.
May I?
You must be angels sent from above!
So your names are Yuuki and Kokkoro, huh?
I think they're after me.
I'm sorry for dragging you two into this.
Yuuki?
Um... Miss Peculiarly Peckish Pecorine?
I will just call you that for now.
There's no going back now,
so let's get out of this together.
Oh! By "Pecorine", do you mean me?
That's a very cute nickname! Crazy cute!
But... I'm happy to know you both feel that way!
May the light's blessing be with you!
I've boosted your agility, my lord.
You should fare much better now!
My lord!
Kokkoro?!
What's this?
It's just like in Lady Ameth's oracle...
How divine!
This is indeed my lord's unique ability—
The proof he is the Princess Knight!
There's more and more power bubbling up inside me!
Is that thanks to Yuuki?
Yes.
Now, let us advance!
Wind spirits, lend us your aid!
Here I come!
Princess Strike!
What a great haul!
I didn't expect us to get this many mushrooms.
Let's gather them all in one place
and talk to Miss Karin.
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
Okay!
A flower field...
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
There's another mushroom right here!
And it's a nice bite-sized one!
Wait! That's—
They taste so good, even raw!
How crazy is that?
M-Miss Pecorine!
Peco, peco...
I'm Pecorine... Pecorine...
She seems to be in good spirits.
I'm glad it wasn't poisonous.
That little one has become
Miss Pecorine's flesh and blood...
Miss Puchi-Pecorine...
It looks like your story has begun at last.
Only the heavens can foretell whether
it will end in tragedy or a happily ever after.
But never forget to ask:
"What are the truths of this world?"
"What are its falsehoods?"
On your journey to uncover these mysteries,
you are sure to meet many faces both new and old.
Alone, your power may not amount to much,
but the allies you make along the way
will become the power necessary to save them all.
This is something only you, the Princess Knight, can do.
Kokkoro.
Yes, my lord?
I'm counting on you.
By all means, my lord.
Seconds, please!