Pudding...
Hand over all your pudding!
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
No, stop... I'm already full...
Enjoy the food!
We went through a lot,
but all in all, it was a fun holiday.
We have Kokkoro to thank for winning that lottery.
I'm so happy all of you enjoyed the trip.
That aside...
These squid sandwiches aren't half bad.
Wanna go catch another one?
Good luck finding another Kraken.
It feels like we're truly beginning to fulfil our mission
and explore different kinds of food.
It sure does!
The Gourmet Guild feels like a proper guild now!
Lady Karyl!
What's up, Korosuke?
We're going to give the restaurant owner
some squid sandwiches as a souvenir.
Did Pecorine forget to bring it to work today?
She said she was going shopping at the market today.
Since it's perishable, we would like to
get it to him as soon as possible.
Okay.
I'm still a bit pooped,
so count on me for the house sitting.
Okay. Please take care of things here.
Come look at our goods!
Ey, come check out some nice fish 'ere!
Bananas freshly harvested from the Ceres Forest!
They taste bananas!
Care for some shaved ice from the Prigga Snowfields?
Everything looks so delicious. It's so exciting!
I hope he'll enjoy our souvenir.
Yep.
Good morning.
Eep!
What's the deal with you today, boss?!
Make something that'll actually fill our bellies,
like bugs or something!
Pudding...
He looks pale.
Are we ever glad to see you!
You guys gotta come snap the boss out of it!
All he does is make pudding!
He hasn't slept one bit!
He's gonna keel over if this keeps up!
Perhaps you should rest a bit.
Pudding!
Don't stop me! Don't you dare stop me!
I can hear it. It's telling me to make more pudding!
My lord?
Something's there.
I don't see anything.
You can see
what's up there.
Who might you be?
I'm a fortune teller in this town.
My name is Shinobu.
I heard a rumour that this restaurant's owner
was making pudding as if possessed,
so I came to check it out.
Pudding... Pudding...
And it appears I met someone
I wasn't expecting to.
What do you mean by that?
Miyako, this person might just
end up being our saviour.
Miyako?
Nobody cares! Just give me my pudding!
I-Is that...
...a ghost?!
PriConne!
This is so yummy!
Temperature is everything when making pudding...
I was thinking about cursing him to death
when he started garnishing my pudding with bugs,
but look at that! Whispering him some orders
to whip up a lot of pudding was the right call after all!
Teeth are everything to celebrities...
You shouldn't possess people so whimsically, Miyako.
Sure, whatever you say.
Miss Shinobu...
Err, is it fine if I call you that?
Could this lady perhaps be a ghost?
She may have an abnormal attachment to pudding,
but yes. She's a ghost.
What do you want?
This pudding's all mine. No sharing!
I had no idea ghosts could be so cutesy.
Having seen Yuuki's power to sense this ghost for myself,
I would like to ask him a favour.
Would you accompany us to
the house of our guild, Diabolos?
I had no idea all this was happening
while we were on holiday.
Come on!
Less talking, more pudding transporting!
Here it is.
This is quite an unusual guild house.
I love how dark and cool it is. It feels so nice.
I see.
Sh-Shinobu, what are you doing?
H-How could you bring outsiders here?
Please be calm.
This man might be the one
who can make our ambition a reality.
You mean...
The complete resurrection of
our queen of the denizens of darkness,
the Legendary Vampire.
Th-That was a lot of rather unsettling words.
My lord, we should take our leave for today.
Where do you plan on going?
Those who dare infiltrate my castle,
I shall grant you the honour of an audience with me.
Welcome, child of man and child of elf.
I am she who rules the night: Illya Ornstein.
I sense an enormous amount
of magic within that crystal.
This is...
You can tell?
This is but a fragment of my power, elf girl.
No need to tense up.
It's not as if I'll gobble you up.
Illya, this man is...
I am aware.
Through the eyes of my minions, I have seen all.
The power you possess
may prove useful in my complete resurrection.
My lord!
Bow before me!
Do you not realise who I am?
You stand before the Legendary Vampire...
Illya Ornstein!
Your body's age still rewinds once you step foot
outside the coffin you were sealed in.
You're so tiny and adorbs.
I'm not tiny!
In truth, this "Legendary Vampire"
is the queen of all demons.
She led them in battle against the human,
elf, and beast races in ancient times.
Then she lost in the final battle of the gods
and was sealed away, so we broke her seal...
But since she's got like, no magic at all,
she deflates constantly. Look at how tiny she is!
As I keep telling you, I'm not tiny!
I understand.
However, I cannot allow any harm to befall my lord.
Oh, worried about that? Don't be.
I told you I'm not gonna eat you or anything.
I'm unsure of what power lies dormant within you
that allows you to sense Miyako's spirit energy,
but it may be the key to restoring my power.
There's nothing there.
What?!
You got our hopes up for nothing?!
Make me the cutest girl in the world already!
Finish your dumb resurrection
and bring me back to life already!
M-My secret wish...
For crying out loud, shut up!
How dare you defile my ears so?!
If anything, I'm the one in tears right now!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Illya...
What good are you if your minions can overthrow you?
They refuse to yield before me!
I can't believe my magic has dwindled so!
My lord?
What are you thinking?
You're making me seem a little child!
Put me down!
Th-This is...
What does this mean?
What mechanisms are at play?
Illya returned to her original form!
Very well, I shall not question.
It is time you were put in your place.
Let me show you who your master is!
Such highly potent magic...
If she wields such power, does that mean
she truly is the Legendary Vampire?
Now, my minions,
return to the shadows.
Yay! Yay!
Now that your magic has been restored,
will you finally be granting our wishes?
You're the best!
Naturally! Do not fear!
Now that my resurrection has been completed,
nothing is impossible for me!
I will now use my magic and my restored body,
and take over the world!
Wh-Why?!
Back to square one we go.
Just when everything seemed to be going fine...
I look like a child again!
Look at how tiny you are!
Hey! Stop calling me tiny!
Shall we take our leave while we have the chance?
Where do you think you're going?
Do you have any idea what you've done?
Don't play stupid games with me!
Just look at the gruesome state
you've left my pudding in!
The pudding was innocent...
You deserve certain death!
I'm gonna curse you!
How long are they gonna take?
She sure is taking her sweet time shopping.
And how long does it take
to give someone a souvenir?
We have returned!
Meep!
Took you long enough! What were you—
Want me to make pudding out of you, too?
And you are?
Pleased to meet you. My name is Shinobu.
I'm Miyako and I'm a ghost!
All your pudding belongs to me!
How the heck did you get possessed on a delivery trip?!
What if we all end up cursed?!
Lady Karyl, I can explain this.
I don't get it, but I kinda do.
So you're supposed to make pudding for her
to replace the pudding you ruined?
Mhm!
"Mhm", my ass!
Don't just put more work on our lap!
Please calm down, Lady Karyl.
Miss Miyako is not an evil spirit.
Right she is. I'm a very friendly ghost.
Stay back!
Stay away from me!
Please, I beg of you! Don't curse me!
The theatre's been torn down again!
An official notice from Princess Eustania herself?
It's one of the few pleasures us
commoners have. I don't understand...
Hey, Peco lady!
Charlie and Ikacchi!
And the boss, too!
How unusual to see you all here.
Man, today was a rough one!
Boss here got possessed by a ghost!
A ghost?
Don't worry about him, though.
Yuuki was able to exorcise it for us.
Yuuki did that?
So we're drinking to celebrate his recovery!
What're you doing, drinking out here
during the day, you nincompoop?!
I don't have the money to let
a fool like you dine here on my dime!
S-Sorry, Mama!
Mama?!
Come one, come all.
Come all.
We got some quality stuff.
Good stuff.
You must be Pecorine, then.
My fool of a son told me all about you.
Sounds like you've come through for him quite a bit.
Thank you.
Hey, you got yourself a pretty little poster girl now!
I oughta hire a young'un like her at my place.
Shut yo' filthy mouth!
If you got time to blabber that junk,
don't leave your customers waiting!
Sure, sure. I'm no match for you, Yasuko.
By the way,
I heard you've travelled to lots of places.
Sounds like a fine way to spend your youth.
I wish my foolish son
was even half as resourceful.
Really...
My parents taught me all I know.
It's because of them that I got to experience so much.
Is that so?
And you came home so grown-up and dependable.
Your folks must be thrilled.
I hope so...
You got a new counter girl?!
Oh, man!
She's lovely.
You're going slack-jawed.
One monster radish, please.
I'd like three island leeks.
Would you look at this?
Sure is getting busy here now.
If only it was always like this.
Ugh!
Where the hell is Pecorine when you need her?!
Shut that little mouth of yours
and get those hands stirring!
Else I'll curse you!
P-Please don't!
Since Lady Pecorine is a splendid cook,
I'm sure she could have made Miss Miyako happy.
What is this horrifying amalgamation
you dare call pudding?
Are you trying to kill me?
Please calm down. You're already dead.
They're all incompetents!
My lord, are you all right?
Disappointment doesn't begin to describe it!
I'm just gonna turn them all
into pudding and eat them!
No!
You're clearly just fooling around! I'll curse you!
If you do that, you'll just be another evil spirit.
Miss Miyako, one of our guildmates
is an excellent cook.
We'll have her make some delicious pudding for you,
so for today, would you—
No! I want my pudding right now!
What do we do?!
Thanks for your help today.
Maybe I really should hire you!
Don't be unreasonable, Mama.
Shut your mouth! You need to
take your work more seriously!
I-I know, Mama!
Now...
Consider this a thank you for today.
Go on, take it home.
Thank you so much!
See you soon!
Peco lady!
Come help out again!
I'm home!
No! I don't wanna be eaten!
What happened to all of you?!
Welcome home, Lady Pecorine.
There are several reasons for this.
Pardon our intrusion.
Who are you?
If you're gonna stop me from eating,
I'll turn you into pudding too!
You turned them all into pudding?
I gave them all this time, and they still
couldn't make any yummy pudding!
Please wait!
I'll make you delicious pudding!
Would you please turn them back to normal?
I don't think so. I've waited long enough.
It will be worth the wait!
I'll make pudding that's better
than any you've ever had!
Th-That good?
I guarantee it!
I'm done!
The Gourmet Guild's special velvety pudding!
I'll try it right now!
The key to making this pudding so velvety
is the temperature of the hot water bath.
Th-The water temperature
makes that much of a difference?
Go on, eat up!
This is the best pudding ever!
It's so velvety soft and rich...
I'm so happy, I feel like my cheeks are melting off!
I finally... I finally found it...
My pudding...
You've finally found your perfect pudding.
Now you can pass on without regret.
I'm so glad.
I got to use Yasuko's gifts straight away!
I apologise for the trouble.
D-Don't worry about it.
Farewell.
Come visit us again sometime!
Wait, where is my lord?
Oh, no!
With all that fuss, he totally slipped my mind!
Yuuki?
Yuuki!
He's not in the living room, either.
Maybe he's out in the bathhouse?
My lord!
Bye-bye.
Am back.