Elder, are you doing well?
I have been hard at work in our guild,
along with my beloved lord,
Lady Pecorine, and Lady Karyl.
In the Village of Targum,
we faced an incident involving
strange monsters known as Shadows.
Nevertheless, we managed to complete
our very first quest successfully.
Ever since, our Gourmet Guild
has completed many more quests.
We have even earned words of praise
from Miss Karin of the Guild Association.
I am beyond blessed to be able to
experience these priceless days.
Hey! Those seedlings aren't properly lined up!
You need to double-check after planting each row!
I'm glad we've got her around.
It's wonderful that Lady Karyl is so meticulous.
Yummy!
Most of Landosol's rice is harvested here, y'know!
It certainly is scenic.
The princess of Landosol loves rice,
so she was determined to start raising rice crops.
I see.
So that's why it's called "princess rice".
Yes!
But it seems animals have been
damaging the paddies a lot lately.
Oh, you mean like wild boars and birds?
Are they eating the crops or something?
Yes, spot on!
The farmer's been trying to shoo them away,
but they just keep coming back.
And that's where we come in!
Our current quest is to
help out the farmer with pest control!
And our reward will be
a handsome amount of princess rice!
Your quests always revolve around food!
Find us a quest with actual rewards!
This quest to help the farmer is wonderful, however.
My lord appears to be having the time of his life!
That's our Lady Ameth scarecrow, Lady Amethy.
My lord and I built them together.
Lady Ameth?
Is that what she looks like?
I guess anything goes so long as Yuuki's
enjoying himself, huh, Korosuke?
Anyway, next time, pick a quest that pays out—
Yummy!
If nothing else, at least you've got
your cooking going for you.
I appreciate the compliments!
That concludes my report on Targum.
Karyl...
Y-Yes?
Are you nervous?
I never told you about the Shadows, did I?
Incidentally, about that boy in your little play-guild...
Yuuki?
I want you to keep a close eye on him as well.
If anything comes to pass, you need only
report to me as you are doing now.
You can do that, can't you,
my sweet Karyl?
Yes...
Your Majesty.
My lord, it's coming your way.
My lord!
Yuuki! Let's have that as
our side dish for supper tonight!
Is there really a reason to bother
observing these clowns?
Karyl, lookie! Let's do this one!
We have to assist some fishermen,
and as a reward, we can eat all the fish we want!
Denied!
What do you think, my lord?
That one?
"Looking for a mentor"?
"We are looking for a kind teacher
to teach us how to work as a guild."
"We'll give you lots of rewards. They're amazing!"
The hell's this?
Oh, that flyer's been posted again?
I'm sorry. I'll take it down now.
Miss Karin...
This is not an officially-approved quest.
I keep taking it down, but the next thing
I know, it's back up again.
You heard her.
So that quest is out, then.
Wah! Wah, wah, wah!
Wah, wah, wah, wah!
Don't cry, Misogi!
You can't give up!
I wonder what that's about.
Probably practising for
a school play or something.
Let's go.
Wah, wah, wah, wah!
Misogi!
Poor Misogi!
Wh-What?!
There's more to the play?
Are you...
interested in that quest, perhaps?
You want us to be your mentors?
Yes. We're not really sure about
what guilds actually do.
So we're looking for someone to guide us!
Please mentor our guild, Little Lyrical!
A bunch of brats play-pretending to be a guild, huh?
We're not pretending!
Oh, are you now?
Why do you want to do guild stuff, anyway?
We want to protect the peace in Landosol.
Anyway, next time, pick a quest that pays out—
As a reward, we can eat all the fish we want!
My lord and I made them together.
I-I totally get you. Truthfully, we feel the same way!
You do?
Peace is very important to Landosol.
Isn't it?!
You three are truly admirable.
N-Not really...
Please, mentor our guild!
Mhm!
Yay!
What's a place that's just safe enough,
just dangerous enough,
and just difficult enough to get through?
I feel like an elementary school teacher
pondering where to go on a field trip.
You would make for a wonderful teacher, Lady Karyl.
Spare me the jokes.
I can't stand kids.
Really?
But you're always very kind to me.
You've got most adults beat in responsibleness.
What about you?
Exactly what are you crafting up there?
You'll find out tomorrow!
I suppose even we can't help
getting excited about this.
What's Yuuki up to?
My lord is preparing the treasure
we'll find at the finish line.
Stand fast!
Count off!
One!
Two!
Three!
Good!
This is the quest you will undertake today!
The treasure is marked on this map.
Make sure you bring it back.
Did you bring the camping gear
we told you to yesterday?
Yes!
Heave-ho.
We have lunch...
...a canteen...
...and snacks!
Yuuki, take good care of them, okay?
Mhm!
Thank you for helping us, Mentor!
You sure they'll be fine?
So long as they follow the map closely,
they won't run into any dangerous monsters.
That's right. Besides, my lord is with them.
I'm worried already.
Hmm... I think we go right?
No, it's this way!
But it looks like the map says to go right.
Look, the compass is pointing left.
No, no!
A compass always points north!
Mentor, could you please
tell us which way to go?
This way?
See?
No, it's the other way!
My lord...
He's so gonna have it when this is over!
What's wrong, Mimi? Why are you yelling?
C-Calm down, guys!
I'll take care of these monsters!
M-Monsters...?
For crying out loud, they're already panicking.
Mentor!
Darn you!
Take this! And that! And some of this!
Good luck!
Let's fight with her!
R-Right!
Hey, Yuuki!
Wrong way!
The other way! It's the other way!
Please turn back!
Oh!
Mentor!
We beat the monsters!
Nice!
Mentor, do we go this way next?
Okay! Off we go!
Yeah!
No, not that way!
M-My lord!
Wh-What shall we do?
So much for my perfectly designed route...
I was prepared for this.
We'll use this.
Are there any naaaaaughty kids around here?
This path is daaaaaangerous!
A monster?!
I-It's so big!
You'd better turn back or I'll eat you for dinner!
It doesn't sound like a joke at all
when she's the one saying it.
I'll gobble you all up!
So this is what she was busy with last night.
I'll slurp you right up and swallow you whole!
We can't just cower in fear!
If we fight hard, like before...
Y-Yeah!
Huh?
Take this! Pepper Bomb!
My eyes! My eyes!
Mimi! Kyouka! Now!
Owwie!
They seem much more coordinated than before.
Kids sure grow up fast.
My eyes! I can't see!
My eyes!
We did it!
How did little kids get the better of you?!
This is bad news!
They're just straying further and further
from the right path!
What will happen if they
keep heading in this direction?
They'll run into many a scare.
What?!
Mentor!
Mentor?!
My lord!
We have to save our mentor!
Grim Burst!
Huh?
Did we beat it?
You're so cool, Mentor!
Eat this!
Enjoy the food!
Yummy!
Eating outside makes it taste even better!
Your lunch looks so cute, Mimi!
Why are we stuck with monster slaying now?
I'm starting to get hungry.
Karyl! Kokkoro!
Don't scare us like that, Dumborine!
I'm sorry, but I can't get this costume off.
More importantly,
they're heading toward a giant monster bird's nest!
They're in danger!
A monster bird's nest?
I come here to collect its eggs occasionally.
They're super tasty!
You really liked the fried eggs
I made the other day, right?
Yummy!
Those were monster eggs?!
Why'd you feed me that?!
It would be for the best if we called off the quest.
Mentor!
My lord!
What is that dumbass doing?!
Give our mentor back!
Cosmo Blue Flash!
Mentor!
I'm scared...
We have to work together to beat that thing!
Yes!
Trick Bomber!
Bunny Slash!
Cosmo Blue Flash!
That's its nest!
Do you see those kids?
There they are!
They're out cold!
Where's my lord?
My lord!
And... Lady Amethy?
So this is the pest we were supposed to control?
No wonder the farmer was powerless to stop it.
Oh, crap!
Grim Burst!
Perfect, Lady Karyl! Hit it with more magic!
N-No can do.
Excuse me?
I've been fighting monsters all freaking day.
I'm absolutely drained.
Aren't you pooped too, Korosuke?
When'd you become such a weakling?!
I-I'm so hungry, my strength's all gone!
I skipped out on lunch
because I was stuck in this costume!
That costume will be the death of us!
Oh?
P-Pecorine!
L-Lady Pecorine!
Yum!
Those girls will make fine adventurers!
Full power!
Full throttle!
Princess Strike!
Did we...
...do that?
We beat it!
Yay!
Not half bad, kiddos.
Mentor!
We completed our quest!
You've done wonderfully.
We have nothing more to teach you.
So, where's the treasure?
Korosuke, where's the treasure?
At the original finish line.
The treasure is
this egg!
Yay!
Let's all have some delicious fried eggs together!
Oh, dear?
It's so cute!
It's so fluffy!
You want to eat that thing?
I guess that's out of the question now.
Um...
You were all acting during this quest, right?
You figured us out, huh?
Thank you so much.
I won't tell the other two, okay?
Mentor—No, Yuuki. Thank you so much.
You even pretended
that bird caught you for us!
Well, I wouldn't say "pretending", but...
Mhm!
What?!
Why are we back to planting seedlings again?
I told you to find a quest with a decent reward next!
Well, the farmer asked for our help again.
Once these seedlings grow,
I'm calling dibs!
Whee!
It's the mixed duck farming method.
It lets you grow delicious rice, pesticide-free!
Hey, you hooligans!
Don't step on the seedlings!
Ew! Bugs!