motto tanoshikunacchae
Why don't we go have some fun somewhere?
yuuwaku saretara
Let our instincts lead the way
me ga te ga tomaranai
The fun truly never ends, huh?
haihai mattenaide saa start
Yep, yep! No more hold-ups, so let's go!
enryo nante muri da wa
No way we can hold back anymore
morimori shugi desho
Our curiosity's gotten the better of us!
tameshitai desu ne seiippai sukoshi
Longing for adventure has gotten you good, am I right?
daitan ni arekore wo
Don't let go of that feeling!
bouken shitai n desu everyday
Don't you wanna venture out every day?
dakara tobidashite
You do? Then come on, let's go!
tobidashite ii yo ne
No holding back, you hear me?
minna sore ga daisuki
We all love going out over here!
Connecting Happy!!
tsunagaru omoi de
On the same wavelength, you and I
itsumo kimi to ima wo kanjitetai na dayo ne da ne
All our shared moments are something to look forward to, don't you agree?
doko ni itemo atsumacchae dakara ne
Forever friends, all of us! Nothing can tear us apart anymore
minna de kyou wa oishii mono demo
Always on the hunt for hip, new delicacies
tabete tabeta ato de
Savour each and every one of 'em
mata raran ue to doka e runaway
Can't stop us now, fate's runaways, get away!
sorezore no hoppeta ga happy
Our faces stuffed to the brim with sunshine!