Lady Pecorine, you're all right!
Where are we?
This is...
Landosol Castle.
We're in Landosol's Castle?
I think so, yeah.
But there's no one here,
so I'm not entirely sure.
What about this portrait?
I'm sorry.
I've been hiding something from you guys.
My name isn't Pecorine.
It's Eustiana von Astraea.
I'm the princess of Landosol.
But...
Yes, the one everyone calls "Her Majesty"
is named Eustiana, too.
I'm someone...
everyone has forgotten about.
Including my parents.
Eustiana.
Mother!
Father!
The time has come at last.
The world is vast.
Hear the voices of our people with your own ears,
see what this nation is like with your own eyes,
and experience what life has to offer it for yourself.
Once you return from your journey,
you will have matured enough
to be a ruler worthy of ruling this nation.
Okay.
Eustiana.
This is a gift from me.
This tiara is one of the royal accessories
handed down in Landosol for generations.
It will surely keep you safe.
The only catch is that using
it will make you very hungry!
I look forward to it! I love to eat!
I'll be off now.
Safe travels.
I got to experience many great things
while travelling around the continent of Astraea.
But when I completed my journey
and returned to Landosol...
I, Eustiana has returned!
I wish to see my parents!
Who do you think you're fooling?
You dare utter Princess Eustiana's name, you ruffian?!
H-Huh? What's happened to all of you?
It's me! Don't you recognise me?
Damn it!
Get her!
Impossible!
We have an intruder!
I-I'm sorry!
You're Mother's meal attendant!
I'm glad to see you again!
It's me, Eustiana—
Does anyone remember me? Anyone?!
It's me! Eustiana!
Did everyone forget me?
Please, somebody!
I have returned from my journey.
I've heard the voices of our people with my own ears,
and seen Landosol with my very own eyes.
Does this mean I still haven't done enough,
Mother, Father?
Who...
...might you be?
I hear the squeaking of a little intruder,
Mother, Father.
Ah, Eustiana!
Do not worry.
I will exterminate this little rat for you.
I managed to escape from the person
who had stolen my name,
and set out on another journey.
A journey without end.
And that's when I met you, Yuuki, and Karyl.
I was so happy. Life was wonderful.
I met all of you,
ate delicious meals...
But I was always afraid.
Afraid that everyone would forget me again.
That the happier I felt,
the more you'd distance yourselves from me.
If I'd told you the truth,
that I was really Eustiana...
I was scared that...
So that's why.
That's why you would always
hug the people important to you so much.
By doing that, you could clamp
all the connections you made together.
If only I had told the truth.
I was so preoccupied with my own world.
And because I was stuck,
because of my selfishness...
I pushed Karyl away from me.
I won't leave you.
Whether you're Princess Eustiana
or Lady Pecorine,
the days we've spent together
as the Gourmet Guild
form an invaluable bond
unlike any other treasure to me.
I'm sure my lord feels the same way.
And not just us, but Lady Karyl as well.
Is it okay if...
Is it okay if we stay like this for a little bit?
Dumborine...
I'd say those girls are figuring out
new truths as well right about now.
Please trust me. I'm not your enemy.
Though, I guess I've dragged you in
too deep to be an ally.
Well, have I ever.
This space we're in is one I built.
Does it look familiar?
Ameth...
That's right. She goes by "Ameth" now.
She's had your back through all this, right?
She's so sweet.
There are signs she's trying to slowly
and carefully restore your memories.
Are you ready?
This power is meant to protect your friends,
but it's also capable of destroying you from within.
At the moment you seem to have
lost most of your memories.
Whether that's because of the Re:Dive
or not remains unclear.
Nevertheless, if you unleash this power as you are now,
there's no telling how it would
affect your very existence itself.
It probably influenced that earlier fight, too.
Shadows attack people to consume their souls.
They've already wiped out entire villages.
And, more than likely,
they showed up wherever you guys were
in search of more powerful souls.
Those things don't just show up by accident.
The will of something, or someone,
allows them to take shape.
As long as you're trapped in this world,
you can never escape that will.
This world came to be as a result of
the battle between you and that will.
You mean...
These memories...
Peco lady!
It's no use! I don't see her anyway!
Quit your whining!
I know she's gotta be a-okay!
Get your butts into gear and find her!
But where could she be?!
Fall back!
This place is still dangerous.
All civilians, stand back!
It's Nightmare!
Shut up!
You always show up right when it's over!
You don't have to put it like that!
We're doing our best here!
Stop that, Matsuri.
What good does it do to argue with
the very civilians we are meant to protect?
But...
She's right.
We mustn't lose sight of our goal.
Jun...
Aren't you... the captain of the palace knights?
Captain.
Tomo, did you find anything?
According to eyewitnesses,
there was a swordswoman who fought
the monster to protect the townsfolk.
However, they say she abruptly
vanished along with the monster.
Vanished?
Yes.
As for the monster...
It shared many similarities with the
Shadows we've had trouble with recently.
What?
Wow, someone put on quite a show here.
Looks like it was even more powerful
than the one I reported before.
Vice Captain...
A swordswoman who protected the people from
a monster like that with no casualties, eh?
She interests me much more
than these cretins do, that's for sure.
Chris, I respect how nonchalant you can be
concerning other people's opinions about you,
but I need you to focus on your job right now.
My apologies, Captain.
But doesn't this strike you as a little odd?
A monster capable of doing this much damage
found its way into Landosol,
the royal capital of Astraea,
and yet we were none the wiser
until long after it had disappeared?
What do you suppose His Majesty is thinking,
deep in that castle of his?
Christina...
Whoops. Don't mind me, just talking to myself.
Pay it no mind.
Oh, while I'm busy thinking out loud anyway...
This is the kingdom of humans, Landosol,
so how and when did a beast
find its way upon its throne, I wonder?
Rising Tempest!
I'm getting in Her Majesty's way again.
But...
What do you want from me?
How am I supposed to choose?!
Right now, I want...
When did I end up like this?
I devoted my entire existence
to Her Majesty alone...
I'm helpless, aren't I?
I really am utterly helpless.
I'm sorry.
You were totally right. I am very selfish.
So...
I want you to help me defeat that monster!
Moron.
Sorry.
I know I threw a lot at you
in such a short amount of time.
But it's all right.
All of us in Labyrinth
will protect you and your friends.
I'll protect them.
I'll protect my friends.
I took such a long way around
to finally see you in person,
and it looks like it was well worth it.
Master, we can't hold out much longer!
Our brother's friends are in trouble!
What should we do?
Should we jump in and help them, even if
that means we give ourselves away to the enemy?
No need, it looks like all the pieces
have finally fallen into place.
And with that, let's do this!
This is my power,
Object Transformation.
I'll lend you just a bit of it
so you can move forward.
I have faith that the bonds you build
will save all of them from this world.
Yuuki?!
Yuuki!
My lord!
Let's go, everyone!
This power...
My magic power...
My lord's feelings...
May the light's blessing be with you!
Princess Strike!
I hope you're ready for this!
Grim Burst!
Grant my lord a body of steel.
Grant my lord the speed of a falcon.
Now, let us advance!
To victory!
Excellent swordsmanship,
my Princess Knight.
Quit crying, you nincompoops!
But... But...
If Peco lady and her friends are gone...
Don't even think about it!
But, Mama...
If you've got the time to cry,
get your butt to work!
Also, that's "Mom" to you!
Peco lady!
You're okay!
Karyl.
Thank you for honouring my selfish request.
That was the last time, okay?
I know!
I love you, Karyl!
Bread really is best with runny eggs!
It sure is!
It makes me feel the joy of a fresh morning.
Your appetite has grown quite healthy, my lord.
I'm beyond delighted.
That's right.
He's no longer the little beansprout
he was when we first met.
Mhm!
What's the plan today?
That's easy!
What's the goal of the Gourmet Guild?
The study of all the delicious food in this world!
Indeed!
It's time to set off.
Onto our next adventure!